<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
<string name="prefs_section_basics">"Båšîçš - one"</string>
<string name="prefs_section_advanced">"Åðvåñçéð - one"</string>
<string name="enter_vr">"Éñţér V® - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_group_general">"Ĝéñéråļ - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_group_sites">"Šîţéš - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_incognito">"Îñçöĝñîţö - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_sharing">"Šĥårîñĝ - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_browser">"Bröŵšér - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_screen_capture">"Šçrééñ Çåþţûré - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_content_suggestions">"Çöñţéñţ Šûĝĝéšţîöñš - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_fullscreen_controls">"Fûļļ šçrééñ šîţé çöñţröļš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="notification_category_sites">"Šîţéš - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_vr">"Vîrţûåļ ®éåļîţý - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_updates">"Ûþðåţéš - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_announcement">"Åññöûñçéméñţš - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_webapps">"Ŵéb åþþš - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_webapps_quiet">"Ŵéb åþþš (qûîéţ) - one two three"</string>
<string name="notification_category_permission_requests">"Þérmîššîöñ réqûéšţš - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_price_drop">"Þrîçé ðröþ åļérţš - one two three"</string>
<string name="notification_category_security_key">"Šîĝñ-îñ vérîƒîçåţîöñš - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_feature_guide">"Çĥrömé ţîþš - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_category_bluetooth">"Bļûéţööţĥ - one"</string>
<string name="notification_category_usb">"ÛŠB - one"</string>
<string name="prefs_section_account_and_google_services">"Ýöû åñð Ĝööĝļé - one two three"</string>
<string name="sign_in_to_chrome">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="prefs_manage_sync_settings_content_description">"Ýöû åré çûrréñţļý çûšţömîžîñĝ ýöûr Šýñç šéţţîñĝš. Ţö ƒîñîšĥ ţûrñîñĝ öñ šýñç, ţåþ ţĥé Çöñƒîrm bûţţöñ ñéår ţĥé böţţöm öƒ ţĥé šçrééñ. Ñåvîĝåţé ûþ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="signin_pref_summary">"Šýñç åñð þéršöñåļîžé åçröšš ðévîçéš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sign_in_to_chrome_disabled_summary">"Ðîšåbļéð bý ţĥé åðmîñîšţråţör öƒ ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sign_in_google_activity_controls_title">"Ĝööĝļé åçţîvîţý çöñţröļš - one two three"</string>
<string name="sign_in_google_activity_controls_summary">"Çöñţröļ ĥöŵ ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý îš ûšéð ţö þéršöñåļîžé Šéårçĥ åñð möré - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="sign_out_and_turn_off_sync">"Šîĝñ öûţ åñð ţûrñ öƒƒ šýñç - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="turn_off_sync">"Ţûrñ öƒƒ šýñç - one two three"</string>
<string name="sign_out">"Šîĝñ öûţ - one two"</string>
<string name="manage_your_google_account">"Måñåĝé ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_category_title">"Šýñç - one"</string>
<string name="prefs_google_services">"Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš - one two"</string>
<string name="allow_chrome_signin_title">"Åļļöŵ Çĥrömé šîĝñ-îñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="allow_chrome_signin_summary">"Šĥöŵš þrömþţš ţö šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="autocomplete_searches_and_urls_title">"Åûţöçömþļéţé šéårçĥéš åñð Û®Ļš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="autocomplete_searches_and_urls_summary">"Šéñðš šömé çööķîéš åñð šéårçĥéš ƒröm ţĥé åððréšš bår åñð šéårçĥ böx ţö ýöûr ðéƒåûļţ šéårçĥ éñĝîñé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="settings_incognito_tab_lock_title">"Ļöçķ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš ŵĥéñ ýöû ļéåvé Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="settings_incognito_tab_lock_summary_android_setting_on">"Ûšé šçrééñ ļöçķ ţö šéé öþéñ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="settings_incognito_tab_lock_summary_android_setting_off">"&lt;link&gt;Ţûrñ öñ šçrééñ ļöçķ îñ Åñðröîð šéţţîñĝš&lt;/link&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="prefs_section_preload_pages_title">"Þréļöåð Þåĝéš - one two"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_title">"Þréļöåð þåĝéš - one two"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_summary">"Ýöû çåñ bröŵšé åñð šéårçĥ ƒåšţér ŵĥéñ Çĥrömé þréļöåðš þåĝéš ţĥåţ îţ ţĥîñķš ýöû mîĝĥţ vîšîţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_no_preloading_title">"Ñö þréļöåðîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_no_preloading_summary">"Þåĝéš ļöåð öñļý åƒţér ýöû öþéñ ţĥém. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_standard_preloading_title">"Šţåñðårð þréļöåðîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_standard_preloading_subtitle">"Šţåñðårð þréļöåðîñĝ: - one two"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_standard_preloading_summary">"Šömé öƒ ţĥé þåĝéš ýöû vîšîţ åré þréļöåðéð. Þåĝéš måý bé þréļöåðéð ţĥröûĝĥ Ĝööĝļé šérvérš ŵĥéñ ļîñķéð ƒröm å Ĝööĝļé šîţé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_standard_preloading_bullet_one">"Þréļöåðš þåĝéš ţĥåţ Çĥrömé ţĥîñķš ýöû åré ļîķéļý ţö vîšîţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_standard_preloading_bullet_two">"Îƒ ýöû åļļöŵ çööķîéš, Çĥrömé måý ûšé ţĥém ƒör þréļöåðîñĝ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_standard_preloading_bullet_three">"Ŵĥéñ å Ĝööĝļé šîţé åšķš ţö þrîvåţéļý þréļöåð ļîñķš öñ ţĥéîr þåĝé, Çĥrömé éñçrýþţš åñð þréļöåðš þåĝéš ţĥröûĝĥ Ĝööĝļé šérvérš ŵîţĥöûţ çööķîéš. Ţĥîš ĥîðéš ýöûr îðéñţîţý ƒröm ţĥé þréļöåðéð šîţé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_standard_preloading_bullet_four">"Béçåûšé ţĥé þréļöåðéð þåĝéš åré éñçrýþţéð, åñð ţĥé šîţé ļîñķîñĝ ţö ţĥé þåĝéš îš å Ĝööĝļé šîţé, Ĝööĝļé šérvérš ðöñ’ţ réçéîvé ñéŵ îñƒörmåţîöñ ŵĥéñ þrîvåţéļý þréļöåðîñĝ ţĥéšé þåĝéš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_extended_preloading_title">"Éxţéñðéð þréļöåðîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_extended_preloading_subtitle">"Éxţéñðéð þréļöåðîñĝ: - one two"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_extended_preloading_summary">"Möré þåĝéš åré þréļöåðéð. Þåĝéš måý bé þréļöåðéð ţĥröûĝĥ Ĝööĝļé šérvérš ŵĥéñ réqûéšţéð bý öţĥér šîţéš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_extended_preloading_bullet_one">"Möré ƒréqûéñţļý þréļöåðš þåĝéš ţĥåţ Çĥrömé ţĥîñķš ýöû åré ļîķéļý ţö vîšîţ. Ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ måý réšûļţ îñ îñçréåšéð ðåţå ûšé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_extended_preloading_bullet_two">"Îƒ ýöû åļļöŵ çööķîéš, Çĥrömé måý ûšé ţĥém ƒör þréļöåðîñĝ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_extended_preloading_bullet_three">"Ŵĥéñ å šîţé åšķš ţö þrîvåţéļý þréļöåð ļîñķš öñ ţĥéîr þåĝé, Çĥrömé éñçrýþţš åñð þréļöåðš þåĝéš ţĥröûĝĥ Ĝööĝļé šérvérš ŵîţĥöûţ çööķîéš. Ţĥîš ĥîðéš ýöûr îðéñţîţý ƒröm ţĥé þréļöåðéð šîţé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="preload_pages_extended_preloading_bullet_four">"Béçåûšé ţĥé þréļöåðéð þåĝéš åré éñçrýþţéð, Ĝööĝļé ŵîļļ ñöţ ļéårñ åñýţĥîñĝ åböûţ ţĥé þréļöåðéð þåĝé çöñţéñţ. Ĝööĝļé šérvérš ŵîļļ ļéårñ ŵĥîçĥ šîţéš åré þrîvåţéļý þréļöåðéð. Ţĥîš îñƒörmåţîöñ îš öñļý ûšéð ţö þréļöåð ţĥé þåĝéš, åñð îš ñöţ ļîñķéð ţö öţĥér îñƒörmåţîöñ ƒröm ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="url_keyed_anonymized_data_title">"Måķé šéårçĥéš åñð bröŵšîñĝ béţţér - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="url_keyed_anonymized_data_summary">"Šéñðš Û®Ļš öƒ þåĝéš ýöû vîšîţ ţö Ĝööĝļé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_sync_and_services_link_legacy">"För möré šéţţîñĝš ţĥåţ réļåţé ţö þrîvåçý, šéçûrîţý, åñð ðåţå çöļļéçţîöñ, šéé &lt;link&gt;Šýñç åñð Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš&lt;/link&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_sync_and_services_link_sync_on">"För möré šéţţîñĝš ţĥåţ réļåţé ţö þrîvåçý, šéçûrîţý, åñð ðåţå çöļļéçţîöñ, šéé &lt;link1&gt;Šýñç&lt;/link1&gt; åñð &lt;link2&gt;Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš&lt;/link2&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_sync_and_services_link_sync_off">"För möré šéţţîñĝš ţĥåţ réļåţé ţö þrîvåçý, šéçûrîţý, åñð ðåţå çöļļéçţîöñ, šéé &lt;link&gt;Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš&lt;/link&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="usage_and_crash_reports_title">"Ĥéļþ îmþrövé Çĥrömé\û2019š ƒéåţûréš åñð þérƒörmåñçé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="usage_and_crash_reports_summary">"Åûţömåţîçåļļý šéñðš ûšåĝé šţåţîšţîçš åñð çråšĥ réþörţš ţö Ĝööĝļé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="prefs_metrics_settings">"Ûšåĝé ðåţå - one two"</string>
<string name="manage_metrics_settings">"Måñåĝé ûšåĝé ðåţå šĥårîñĝ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="metrics_settings_description">"Çĥööšé ŵĥåţ ýöû’ré çömƒörţåbļé ţö šĥåré ŵîţĥ Çĥrömé. Ţĥé méţrîçš ýöû šĥåré ŵîļļ bé ûšéð ţö ĥéļþ îmþrövé Çĥrömé’š ƒéåţûréš, þérƒörmåñçé, åñð šţåbîļîţý. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="metrics_settings_extended_title">"Éxţéñðéð ûšåĝé ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="metrics_settings_extended_summary">"Båšîç ðåţå þļûš îñƒörmåţîöñ åböûţ ţĥé ŵébšîţéš ýöû vîšîţ åñð åþþš ýöû ûšé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="metrics_settings_basic_title">"Båšîç ûšåĝé ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="metrics_settings_basic_summary">"Ĥöŵ ýöû îñţéråçţ ŵîţĥ Çĥrömé, šéţţîñĝš ýöû’vé šéļéçţéð, ðéţåîļš öƒ Çĥrömé çråšĥéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="metrics_settings_none_title">"Ñö ûšåĝé ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="metrics_settings_none_summary">"Ñö šţåţîšţîçš ör çråšĥ réþörţš åré šéñţ ţö Ĝööĝļé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="search_engine_settings">"Šéårçĥ éñĝîñé - one two"</string>
<string name="search_engine_recently_visited">"®éçéñţļý vîšîţéð - one two"</string>
<string name="search_engine_dialog_title">"Çĥööšé ýöûr šéårçĥ éñĝîñé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="search_engine_dialog_footer">"Ýöû çåñ çĥåñĝé ţĥîš ļåţér îñ Šéţţîñĝš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="search_engine_choice_prompt">"Ýöû çåñ çĥööšé ýöûr šéårçĥ éñĝîñé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="payment_apps_title">"Þåýméñţ åþþš - one two"</string>
<string name="payment_no_apps_summary">"Ñö šûþþörţéð åþþš îñšţåļļéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="payment_apps_usage_message">"Öñ šömé ŵébšîţéš, ýöû çåñ þåý ŵîţĥ åbövé šûþþörţéð þåýméñţ åþþš öñ ýöûr ðévîçé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="autofill_create_profile">"Åðð åððréšš - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_profile_editor_country">"Çöûñţrý/®éĝîöñ - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_profile_editor_honorific_prefix">"Ţîţļé - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_profile_editor_email_address">"Émåîļ - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_profile_editor_phone_number">"Þĥöñé - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_name">"Ñåmé öñ çårð - one two three"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_nickname">"Çårð ñîçķñåmé - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_invalid_nickname">"Ñîçķñåmé çåñ’ţ îñçļûðé ñûmbérš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="autofill_card_holder_name">"Çårðĥöļðér ñåmé - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_number">"Çårð ñûmbér - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_expiration_date">"Éxþîråţîöñ ðåţé - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_expiration_month">"Éxþîråţîöñ möñţĥ - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_expiration_year">"Éxþîråţîöñ ýéår - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_billing_address">"Bîļļîñĝ åððréšš - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_describe_local_copy">"Çöþîéð ţö Çĥrömé - one two three"</string>
<string name="autofill_payments_authenticator_selection_dialog_title">"Vérîƒý ýöûr çårð - one two three"</string>
<string name="autofill_payments_authenticator_selection_dialog_header">"Ýöûr båñķ ŵåñţš ţö çöñƒîrm îţ\û2019š ýöû. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="autofill_payments_authenticator_selection_dialog_footer">"Ñöţ šééîñĝ ýöûr çûrréñţ îñƒö¿ Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ýöûr båñķ ţö ûþðåţé îţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_payments_authenticator_selection_dialog_progress_bar_message">"Çöñţåçţîñĝ ýöûr båñķ\û2026 - one two three"</string>
<string name="autofill_payments_authenticator_selection_dialog_positive_button_label">"Çöñţîñûé - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_payments_authenticator_selection_dialog_negative_button_label">"Çåñçéļ - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_virtual_card_unenroll_dialog_title">"®émövé ýöûr vîrţûåļ çårð¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_virtual_card_unenroll_dialog_message">"Ýöû’ļļ ñö ļöñĝér bé åbļé ţö ûšé ýöûr vîrţûåļ çårð ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Þåý. &lt;link1&gt;Ļéårñ möré åböûţ vîrţûåļ çårðš&lt;/link1&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_virtual_card_unenroll_dialog_positive_button_label">"®émövé - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_dialog_education_text">"Å vîrţûåļ çårð ĥîðéš ýöûr åçţûåļ çårð ţö ĥéļþ þröţéçţ ýöû ƒröm þöţéñţîåļ ƒråûð. &lt;link1&gt;Ļéårñ möré åböûţ vîrţûåļ çårðš&lt;/link1&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_dialog_card_container_title">"Vîrţûåļ çårð - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_dialog_card_label">"Ļîñķéð ŵîţĥ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_infobar_card_prefix">"ļîñķéð ŵîţĥ - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_card_editor_virtual_card_turn_on_button_label">"Ţûrñ öñ - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_card_editor_virtual_card_turn_off_button_label">"Ţûrñ öƒƒ - one two"</string>
<plurals name="payment_request_payment_methods_preview">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="payment_request_shipping_addresses_preview">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="payment_request_shipping_options_preview">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="payment_request_contacts_preview">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s\û2026 åñð %2$s möré - one two three four five"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="password_settings_title">"Þåššŵörðš - one"</string>
<string name="password_settings_title_gpm">"Þåššŵörð Måñåĝér &lt;new&gt;Ñéŵ&lt;/new&gt; - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="password_settings_save_passwords">"Šåvé þåššŵörðš - one two"</string>
<string name="passwords_auto_signin_title">"Åûţö Šîĝñ-îñ - one two"</string>
<string name="passwords_auto_signin_description">"Åûţömåţîçåļļý šîĝñ îñ ţö ŵébšîţéš ûšîñĝ šţöréð çréðéñţîåļš. Ŵĥéñ ţĥé ƒéåţûré îš öƒƒ, ýöû’ļļ bé åšķéð ƒör vérîƒîçåţîöñ évérý ţîmé béƒöré šîĝñîñĝ îñ ţö å ŵébšîţé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="passwords_leak_detection_switch_title">"Ŵårñ ýöû îƒ þåššŵörðš åré éxþöšéð îñ å ðåţå bréåçĥ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="passwords_leak_detection_switch_signed_out_enable_description">"Ŵĥéñ ýöû šîĝñ îñ ţö ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ, ţĥîš ƒéåţûré îš ţûrñéð öñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="passwords_check_title">"Çĥéçķ þåššŵörðš - one two"</string>
<string name="passwords_check_description">"Ķééþ ýöûr þåššŵörðš šåƒé ƒröm ðåţå bréåçĥéš åñð öţĥér šéçûrîţý îššûéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="android_trusted_vault_banner_label">"Öñ-ðévîçé éñçrýþţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="android_trusted_vault_banner_sub_label_offer_opt_in">"För åððéð šåƒéţý, éñçrýþţ þåššŵörðš öñ ýöûr ðévîçé béƒöré ţĥéý‘ré šåvéð ţö Ĝööĝļé Þåššŵörð Måñåĝér - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="android_trusted_vault_banner_sub_label_opted_in">"Ýöûr þåššŵörðš åré éñçrýþţéð öñ ýöûr ðévîçé béƒöré ţĥéý’ré šåvéð ţö Ĝööĝļé Þåššŵörð Måñåĝér - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="section_saved_passwords_exceptions">"Ñévér šåvéð - one two"</string>
<string name="manage_passwords_text">"Vîéŵ åñð måñåĝé šåvéð þåššŵörðš îñ ýöûr &lt;link&gt;Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ&lt;/link&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="saved_passwords_none_text">"Šåvéð þåššŵörðš ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="password_no_result">"Çåñ’ţ ƒîñð ţĥåţ þåššŵörð. Çĥéçķ ýöûr šþéļļîñĝ åñð ţrý åĝåîñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="password_edit_hint">"Måķé šûré ţĥé þåššŵörð ýöû åré šåvîñĝ måţçĥéš ýöûr þåššŵörð ƒör %1$s - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_edit_deletion_dialog_body">"Ðéļéţîñĝ ţĥîš þåššŵörð ŵîļļ ñöţ ðéļéţé ýöûr åççöûñţ öñ %1$s - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="password_check_delete_credential_dialog_body">"Ðéļéţîñĝ ţĥîš þåššŵörð ŵîļļ ñöţ ðéļéţé ýöûr åççöûñţ öñ %1$s. Çĥåñĝé ýöûr þåššŵörð ör ðéļéţé ýöûr åççöûñţ öñ %1$s ţö ķééþ îţ šåƒé ƒröm öţĥérš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="password_entry_edit_delete_credential_dialog_title">"Ðéļéţé þåššŵörð¿ - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_edit_delete_credential_dialog_confirm">"Ðéļéţé þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_title">"Šåvéð þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_site_title">"Šîţé - one"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_username_title">"Ûšérñåmé - one"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_password">"Þåššŵörð - one"</string>
<string name="password_via_federation">"ŵîţĥ %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_copy_stored_username">"Çöþý ûšérñåmé - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_copy_stored_password">"Çöþý þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_show_stored_password">"Šĥöŵ þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_delete_stored_password_action_title">"Ðéļéţé þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_edit_stored_password_action_title">"Éðîţ þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_hide_stored_password">"Ĥîðé þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_delete_stored_password">"Ðéļéţé šţöréð þåššŵörð - one two three"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_username_copied_into_clipboard">"Ûšérñåmé çöþîéð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_viewer_password_copied_into_clipboard">"Þåššŵörð çöþîéð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_entry_view_set_screen_lock">"Ţö vîéŵ þåššŵörðš, ƒîršţ šéţ å šçrééñ ļöçķ öñ ýöûr ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="password_entry_copy_set_screen_lock">"Ţö çöþý þåššŵörðš, ƒîršţ šéţ å šçrééñ ļöçķ öñ ýöûr ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="password_entry_edit_duplicate_username_error">"Ýöû åļréåðý šåvéð ţĥîš ûšérñåmé ƒör ţĥîš šîţé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="password_entry_edit_empty_password_error">"Éñţér þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_export_set_lock_screen">"Ţûrñ öñ šçrééñ ļöçķ îñ Šéţţîñĝš ţö éxþörţ ýöûr þåššŵörðš ƒröm ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="password_generation_popup_content_description">"Šĥöŵîñĝ þåššŵörð ĝéñéråţîöñ þöþûþ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_action_title">"Éxþörţ þåššŵörðš… - one two"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_action_description">"Éxþörţ þåššŵörðš šţöréð ŵîţĥ Çĥrömé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="settings_passwords_export_description">"Ýöûr þåššŵörðš ŵîļļ bé éxþörţéð åñð ðöŵñļöåðéð åš å ţéxţ ƒîļé. Ţĥéý ŵîļļ bé vîšîbļé ţö åñýöñé åñð åñý åþþ ŵîţĥ åççéšš ţö ţĥé ðéšţîñåţîöñ ƒöļðér. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="settings_passwords_preparing_export">"Þréþårîñĝ þåššŵörðš… - one two"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_error_title">"Çåñ’ţ éxþörţ þåššŵörðš - one two three"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_learn_google_drive">"Ļéårñ ĥöŵ ţö ûšé Ĝööĝļé Ðrîvé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_no_app">"Ýöûr ðévîçé ðöéšñ’ţ ĥåvé åñ åþþ ţö šţöré ţĥé þåššŵörðš ƒîļé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_tips">"Ţrý ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ ţîþš: måķé šûré ţĥéré îš éñöûĝĥ šþåçé öñ ýöûr ðévîçé, ţrý ţö éxþörţ åĝåîñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_error_details">"Ðéţåîļš: %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="upm_error_notification_title">"Unified password manager error"</string>
<string name="upm_error_notification_contents">"The unified password manager was automatically disabled. Please submit an issue via the bug app!"</string>
<string name="lockscreen_description_copy">"Ûñļöçķ ţö çöþý ýöûr þåššŵörð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="lockscreen_description_view">"Ûñļöçķ ţö vîéŵ ýöûr þåššŵörð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="lockscreen_description_edit">"Ûñļöçķ ţö éðîţ ýöûr þåššŵörð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="lockscreen_description_export">"Ûñļöçķ ţö éxþörţ ýöûr þåššŵörðš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="password_settings_export_subject">"Çĥrömé Þåššŵörðš - one two"</string>
<string name="options_homepage_edit_hint">"Éñţér çûšţöm ŵéb åððréšš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="options_homepage_edit_title">"Éðîţ ĥöméþåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="options_homepage_edit_label">"Öþéñ ţĥîš þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="options_homepage_chrome_homepage">"Çĥrömé’š ĥöméþåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="prefs_notifications">"Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš - one"</string>
<string name="theme_settings">"Ţĥémé - one"</string>
<string name="themes_system_default_title">"Šýšţém ðéƒåûļţ - one two"</string>
<string name="themes_system_default_summary">"Ţûrñ öñ ðårķ ţĥémé ŵĥéñ ýöûr ðévîçé\'š Båţţérý Šåvér îš öñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="themes_system_default_summary_api_29">"Ţûrñ öñ ðårķ ţĥémé ŵĥéñ ýöûr ðévîçé\'š ðårķ ţĥémé ör Båţţérý Šåvér îš öñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="darken_websites">"Åþþļý ðårķ ţĥémé ţö šîţéš, ŵĥéñ þöššîbļé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="prefs_privacy_security">"Þrîvåçý åñð šéçûrîţý - one two three"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_title">"Ţöûçĥ ţö Šéårçĥ - one two three"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_description">"Ļéårñ åböûţ ţöþîçš öñ ŵébšîţéš ŵîţĥöûţ ļéåvîñĝ ţĥé þåĝé. Šéļéçţ öñé ör möré ŵörðš öñ ţĥé þåĝé ţö šéårçĥ ƒör ţĥém. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_promo_title">"Îñçļûðé šûrröûñðîñĝ ţéxţ îñ Ĝööĝļé šéårçĥéš¿ - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_promo_description">"Bý îñçļûðîñĝ möré öƒ å þåĝé’š ţéxţ, ýöû mîĝĥţ šéé béţţér réšûļţš ŵĥéñ ûšîñĝ Ţöûçĥ ţö Šéårçĥ. Ýöû çåñ åļŵåýš vîšîţ &lt;link&gt;šéţţîñĝš&lt;/link&gt; ţö çĥåñĝé ţĥîš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_include_button">"Îñçļûðé - one"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_no_thanks_button">"Ñö ţĥåñķš - one two"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_default_caption">"Ţåþ ţö šéé šéårçĥ réšûļţš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_see_better_results_title">"Îñçļûðé šûrröûñðîñĝ ţéxţ îñ Ĝööĝļé šéårçĥéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_see_better_results_summary">"Bý îñçļûðîñĝ möré öƒ å þåĝé’š ţéxţ, ýöû mîĝĥţ šéé béţţér réšûļţš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="do_not_track_title">"“Ðö Ñöţ Ţråçķ” - one two three"</string>
<string name="do_not_track_description">"Éñåbļîñĝ “Ðö Ñöţ Ţråçķ” méåñš ţĥåţ å réqûéšţ ŵîļļ bé îñçļûðéð ŵîţĥ ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ţråƒƒîç. Åñý éƒƒéçţ ðéþéñðš öñ ŵĥéţĥér å ŵébšîţé réšþöñðš ţö ţĥé réqûéšţ, åñð ĥöŵ ţĥé réqûéšţ îš îñţérþréţéð.

För éxåmþļé, šömé ŵébšîţéš måý réšþöñð ţö ţĥîš réqûéšţ bý šĥöŵîñĝ ýöû åðš ţĥåţ åréñ’ţ båšéð öñ öţĥér ŵébšîţéš ýöû’vé vîšîţéð. Måñý ŵébšîţéš ŵîļļ šţîļļ çöļļéçţ åñð ûšé ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ðåţå — ƒör éxåmþļé ţö îmþrövé šéçûrîţý, ţö þrövîðé çöñţéñţ, åðš åñð réçömméñðåţîöñš, åñð ţö ĝéñéråţé réþörţîñĝ šţåţîšţîçš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="can_make_payment_title">"Åççéšš þåýméñţ méţĥöðš - one two three"</string>
<string name="prefs_privacy_sandbox">"Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_status_enabled">"Ţrîåļ ƒéåţûréš åré öñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_status_disabled">"Ţrîåļ ƒéåţûréš åré öƒƒ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_description_title">"Åböûţ Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_description_two">"Ŵîţĥ &lt;link&gt;Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx&lt;/link&gt;, Çĥrömé îš ðévéļöþîñĝ ñéŵ ţéçĥñöļöĝîéš ţö šåƒéĝûårð ýöû ƒröm çröšš-šîţé ţråçķîñĝ ŵĥîļé þréšérvîñĝ ţĥé öþéñ ŵéb.

Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx ţrîåļš åré šţîļļ îñ åçţîvé ðévéļöþméñţ åñð åré åvåîļåbļé îñ šéļéçţéð réĝîöñš. För ñöŵ, šîţéš måý ţrý öûţ Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx ŵĥîļé çöñţîñûîñĝ ţö ûšé çûrréñţ ŵéb ţéçĥñöļöĝîéš ļîķé ţĥîrð-þårţý çööķîéš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_toggle">"Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx ţrîåļš - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_toggle_description_two">"Ŵĥéñ öñ, šîţéš måý ûšé ţĥé þrîvåçý-þréšérvîñĝ ţéçĥñîqûéš šĥöŵñ ĥéré ţö þrövîðé ţĥéîr çöñţéñţ åñð šérvîçéš. Ţĥéšé îñçļûðé åļţérñåţîvéš ţö çröšš-šîţé ţråçķîñĝ. Möré ţrîåļš måý bé åððéð övér ţîmé.

&lt;li1&gt;Åðvérţîšérš åñð þûbļîšĥérš çåñ ûšé FĻöÇ.&lt;/li1&gt;

&lt;li2&gt;Åðvérţîšérš åñð þûbļîšĥérš çåñ šţûðý ţĥé éƒƒéçţîvéñéšš öƒ åðš îñ å ŵåý ţĥåţ ðöéš ñöţ ţråçķ ýöû åçröšš šîţéš.&lt;/li2&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_snackbar_message">"Ļéårñ åböûţ åñð çöñţröļ ñéŵ ţéçĥñöļöĝîéš ţĥåţ åîm ţö réþļåçé ţĥîrð-þårţý çööķîéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="prefs_privacy_sandbox_floc">"FĻöÇ - one"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_floc_description">"Ţĥîš ţrîåļ îš åçţîvé öñļý îñ &lt;link&gt;šömé réĝîöñš&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_floc_status_title">"Šţåţûš - one"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_floc_group_title">"Ĝröûþ ñûmbér - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_floc_update_title">"Ñéxţ ûþðåţé - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_floc_reset_button">"®éšéţ ĝröûþ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_trials_title">"Ţrîåļš - one"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_description">"Ŵîţĥ Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx ţrîåļš, šîţéš çåñ ðéļîvér ţĥé šåmé bröŵšîñĝ éxþérîéñçé ûšîñĝ ļéšš öƒ ýöûr ðåţå. Ţĥåţ méåñš möré þrîvåçý ƒör ýöû åñð ļéšš çröšš-šîţé ţråçķîñĝ. Ŵé’ļļ åðð ñéŵ ţrîåļš åš ţĥéý’ré réåðý ţö ţéšţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_about_ad_personalization_link">"Åböûţ Bröŵšér-båšéð åð þéršöñåļîžåţîöñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_personalization_title">"Åð þéršöñåļîžåţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_personalization_summary">"Ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý åƒƒéçţš ţĥé åðš ýöû šéé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_personalization_description_trials_on">"Ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý åƒƒéçţš ţĥé åðš ýöû šéé åñð ţĥé îñţéréšţš åš éšţîmåţéð béļöŵ. Ţö þröţéçţ ýöûr þrîvåçý, Çĥrömé åûţö-ðéļéţéš ýöûr îñţéréšţš öñ å röļļîñĝ båšîš éåçĥ möñţĥ. Îñţéréšţš çåñ réƒréšĥ ûñļéšš ýöû rémövé ţĥém. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_personalization_description_no_items">"Îƒ Çĥrömé ĥåš råñðömļý þļåçéð ýöû îñ åñ åçţîvé ţrîåļ, ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý åƒƒéçţš ţĥé åðš ýöû šéé åñð ţĥé îñţéréšţš åš éšţîmåţéð béļöŵ. Ţö þröţéçţ ýöûr þrîvåçý, Çĥrömé ðéļéţéš ýöûr îñţéréšţš öñ å röļļîñĝ båšîš éåçĥ möñţĥ. Îñţéréšţš réƒréšĥ ûñļéšš ýöû rémövé ţĥém. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_personalization_description_trials_off">"Ŵĥéñ ţrîåļš åré öñ åñð îƒ Çĥrömé ĥåš råñðömļý þļåçéð ýöû îñ åñ åçţîvé ţrîåļ, ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý åƒƒéçţš ţĥé åðš ýöû šéé åñð ţĥé îñţéréšţš åš éšţîmåţéð béļöŵ. Ţö þröţéçţ ýöûr þrîvåçý, Çĥrömé ðéļéţéš ýöûr îñţéréšţš öñ å röļļîñĝ båšîš éåçĥ möñţĥ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_measurement_title">"Åð méåšûréméñţ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_measurement_description_trials_on">"Åð méåšûréméñţ åļļöŵš šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ ţö réqûéšţ îñƒörmåţîöñ ƒröm Çĥrömé ţĥåţ ĥéļþš ţĥé šîţé méåšûré ţĥé þérƒörmåñçé öƒ ţĥéîr åðš. Åð méåšûréméñţ réšţrîçţš çröšš-šîţé ţråçķîñĝ bý ţråñšƒérrîñĝ åš ļîţţļé îñƒörmåţîöñ åš þöššîbļé béţŵééñ šîţéš.

Ŵĥéñ ýöû ðéļéţé ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý — åļļ ör ƒör å šþéçîƒîç šîţé — ýöû åļšö ðéļéţé åššöçîåţéð méåšûréméñţ îñƒö. Šéé &lt;link&gt;ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_measurement_description_trials_off">"Ŵĥéñ ţrîåļš åré öñ, Åð méåšûréméñţ åļļöŵš šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ ţö réqûéšţ îñƒörmåţîöñ ƒröm Çĥrömé ţĥåţ ĥéļþš ţĥé šîţé méåšûré ţĥé þérƒörmåñçé öƒ ţĥéîr åðš. Åð méåšûréméñţ réšţrîçţš çröšš-šîţé ţråçķîñĝ bý ţråñšƒérrîñĝ åš ļîţţļé îñƒörmåţîöñ åš þöššîbļé béţŵééñ šîţéš.

Ŵĥéñ ýöû ðéļéţé ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý — åļļ ör ƒör å šþéçîƒîç šîţé — ýöû åļšö ðéļéţé åššöçîåţéð méåšûréméñţ îñƒö. Šéé &lt;link&gt;ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_measurement_summary">"Åðvérţîšérš çåñ ûñðéršţåñð ĥöŵ åðš þérƒörm - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_spam_fraud_title">"Šþåm &amp; ƒråûð réðûçţîöñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_spam_fraud_summary">"Ĥéļþ šîţéš ƒîĝĥţ ƒråûð åñð ðîšţîñĝûîšĥ böţš ƒröm þéöþļé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_spam_fraud_description_trials_on">"Šþåm &amp; ƒråûð réðûçţîöñ réļîéš öñ ţrûšţ ţöķéñš ţö ĥéļþ šîţéš ƒîĝĥţ ƒråûð åñð ðîšţîñĝûîšĥ böţš ƒröm þéöþļé.

Båšéð öñ ýöûr îñţéråçţîöñ ŵîţĥ å šîţé, ļîķé réĝûļårļý šîĝñîñĝ îñ ţö åñ åççöûñţ, ţĥåţ šîţé çåñ îššûé å ţrûšţ ţöķéñ ţö ýöûr bröŵšér. Ļåţér, îƒ öţĥér šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ çĥéçķ ƒör åñð ƒîñð å våļîð ţrûšţ ţöķéñ, ţĥéý’ré möré ļîķéļý ţö ţréåţ ýöû ļîķé å þéršöñ åñð ñöţ å böţ.

Ţrûšţ ţöķéñš îmþrövé þrîvåçý öñ ţĥé ŵéb åñð çåñ’ţ bé ûšéð ţö ƒîñð öûţ ŵĥö ýöû åré. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_spam_fraud_description_trials_off">"Ŵĥéñ ţrîåļš åré öñ, Šþåm &amp; ƒråûð réðûçţîöñ réļîéš öñ ţrûšţ ţöķéñš ţö ĥéļþ šîţéš ƒîĝĥţ ƒråûð åñð ðîšţîñĝûîšĥ böţš ƒröm þéöþļé.

Båšéð öñ ýöûr îñţéråçţîöñ ŵîţĥ å šîţé, ļîķé réĝûļårļý šîĝñîñĝ îñ ţö åñ åççöûñţ, ţĥåţ šîţé çåñ îššûé å ţrûšţ ţöķéñ ţö ýöûr bröŵšér. Ļåţér, îƒ öţĥér šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ çĥéçķ ƒör åñð ƒîñð å våļîð ţrûšţ ţöķéñ, ţĥéý’ré möré ļîķéļý ţö ţréåţ ýöû ļîķé å þéršöñ åñð ñöţ å böţ.

Ţrûšţ ţöķéñš îmþrövé þrîvåçý öñ ţĥé ŵéb åñð çåñ’ţ bé ûšéð ţö ƒîñð öûţ ŵĥö ýöû åré. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_learn_more_description_topics_1">"&lt;b&gt;Ŵĥåţ ðåţå îš ûšéð:&lt;/b&gt; Ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý, å réçörð öƒ šîţéš ýöû’vé vîšîţéð ûšîñĝ Çĥrömé öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_learn_more_description_topics_2">"&lt;b&gt;Ĥöŵ ŵé ûšé ţĥîš ðåţå:&lt;/b&gt; Çĥrömé çåñ éšţîmåţé ýöûr îñţéréšţš. Ļåţér, å šîţé ýöû vîšîţ çåñ åšķ Çĥrömé ţö šéé ýöûr îñţéréšţš îñ örðér ţö þéršöñåļîžé ţĥé åðš ýöû šéé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_learn_more_description_topics_3">"&lt;b&gt;Ĥöŵ ýöû çåñ måñåĝé ýöûr ðåţå:&lt;/b&gt; Ţö þröţéçţ ýöûr þrîvåçý, ŵé åûţö-ðéļéţé ýöûr îñţéréšţš ţĥåţ åré öļðér ţĥåñ 4 ŵééķš. Åš ýöû ķééþ bröŵšîñĝ, åñ îñţéréšţ mîĝĥţ åþþéår öñ ţĥé ļîšţ åĝåîñ. Ör ýöû çåñ rémövé îñţéréšţš ýöû ðöñ’ţ ŵåñţ Çĥrömé ţö çöñšîðér. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_learn_more_description_fledge_1">"&lt;b&gt;Ŵĥåţ ðåţå îš ûšéð:&lt;/b&gt; Ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý, å réçörð öƒ šîţéš ýöû’vé vîšîţéð ûšîñĝ Çĥrömé öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_learn_more_description_fledge_2">"&lt;b&gt;Ĥöŵ ŵé ûšé ţĥîš ðåţå:&lt;/b&gt; Šîţéš çåñ šţöré îñƒörmåţîöñ ŵîţĥ Çĥrömé åböûţ ýöûr îñţéréšţš. För éxåmþļé, îƒ ýöû vîšîţ å šîţé ţö bûý šĥöéš ƒör å måråţĥöñ, ţĥé šîţé mîĝĥţ ðéƒîñé ýöûr îñţéréšţ åš rûññîñĝ måråţĥöñš. Ļåţér, îƒ ýöû vîšîţ å ðîƒƒéréñţ šîţé ţö réĝîšţér ƒör å råçé, ţĥåţ šîţé çåñ šĥöŵ ýöû åñ åð ƒör rûññîñĝ šĥöéš båšéð öñ ýöûr îñţéréšţš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_learn_more_description_fledge_3">"&lt;b&gt;Ĥöŵ ýöû çåñ måñåĝé ýöûr ðåţå:&lt;/b&gt; Ţö þröţéçţ ýöûr þrîvåçý, ŵé åûţö-ðéļéţé šîţéš ƒröm ţĥé ļîšţ ţĥåţ åré öļðér ţĥåñ 4 ŵééķš. Å šîţé ýöû vîšîţ åĝåîñ mîĝĥţ åþþéår öñ ţĥé ļîšţ åĝåîñ. Ör ýöû çåñ rémövé å šîţé îƒ ýöû ðöñ’ţ ŵåñţ ţĥåţ šîţé ţö évér ðéƒîñé îñţéréšţš ƒör ýöû. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_learn_more_title">"Åböûţ åð þéršöñåļîžåţîöñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_add_interest_button_description">"Åðð %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_add_site_button_description">"Åðð %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_add_interest_snackbar">"Çĥrömé çåñ çöñšîðér ţĥîš îñţéréšţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_add_site_snackbar">"Šîţé çåñ ðéƒîñé îñţéréšţš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_remove_interest_button_description">"®émövé %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_remove_site_button_description">"®émövé %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_remove_interest_snackbar">"Îñţéréšţ rémövéð - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_remove_interest_title">"Îñţéréšţš ýöû rémövéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_remove_site_snackbar">"Šîţé rémövéð - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_remove_sites_title">"Šîţéš ýöû rémövéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_remove_interest_description">"Åļļöŵ åñ îñţéréšţ ör šîţé îƒ ýöû ţĥîñķ åðš réļåţéð ţö ţĥé îţém ŵöûļð bé ûšéƒûļ ţö ýöû - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_ad_personalization_subtitle">"Bröŵšér-båšéð åð þéršöñåļîžåţîöñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_topic_interests_subtitle">"Ýöûr îñţéréšţš åš éšţîmåţéð bý Çĥrömé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_fledge_interests_subtitle">"Šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ ţĥåţ ðéƒîñé ýöûr îñţéréšţš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_topic_empty_state">"Å ļîšţ öƒ îñţéréšţš ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré åš ýöû bröŵšé ţĥé ŵéb - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_removed_topics_empty_state">"Îñţéréšţš ýöû rémövéð ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_removed_sites_empty_state">"Šîţéš ýöû rémövéð ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_fledge_subtitle">"Šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ ţĥåţ ðéƒîñé ýöûr îñţéréšţš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_fledge_empty_state">"Å ļîšţ öƒ šîţéš ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré åš ýöû bröŵšé ţĥé ŵéb - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_dialog_no_button">"Ñö ţĥåñķš - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_dialog_yes_button">"Ýéš, Î’m îñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_dialog_acknowledge_button">"Ĝöţ îţ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_dialog_settings_button">"Šéţţîñĝš - one"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_title">"Ĥéļþ ûš bûîļð å möré þrîvåţé ŵéb - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_subtitle">"Çĥrömé îš éxþļörîñĝ ñéŵ ƒéåţûréš ţĥåţ åļļöŵ šîţéš ţö ðéļîvér ţĥé šåmé bröŵšîñĝ éxþérîéñçé ûšîñĝ ļéšš öƒ ýöûr îñƒö - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_heading_one">"Ļîmîţéð šĥårîñĝ béţŵééñ šîţéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_description_one">"Ŵé’ré éxþļörîñĝ ŵåýš ţö réšţrîçţ ţråçķîñĝ ŵĥîļé éñåbļîñĝ šîţéš ţö šţöþ åð šþåm åñð ƒråûð. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_heading_two">"Möré çöñţröļ övér ţĥé åðš ýöû šéé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_description_two">"Ýöû çåñ šéé åñð rémövé ţöþîçš öƒ îñţéréšţ šîţéš ûšé ţö šĥöŵ ýöû åðš. Çĥrömé éšţîmåţéš ýöûr îñţéréšţš båšéð öñ ýöûr réçéñţ bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_dropdown_button">"Ļéårñ möré åböûţ åð þéršöñåļîžåţîöñ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_dropdown_topics_heading">"Ýöûr îñţéréšţš åš éšţîmåţéð bý Çĥrömé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_dropdown_fledge_heading">"Šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ ţĥåţ ðéƒîñé ýöûr îñţéréšţš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_consent_description_three">"Ýöû çåñ çĥåñĝé ýöûr mîñð åţ åñý ţîmé îñ Çĥrömé šéţţîñĝš. Ţĥé ţrîåļš rûñ åļöñĝšîðé ţĥé çûrréñţ ŵåý åðš ĝéţ šérvéð, šö ýöû ŵöñ’ţ šéé çĥåñĝéš rîĝĥţ åŵåý. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_notice_description_three">"Ýöû çåñ ļéårñ möré åböûţ ţĥéšé ƒéåţûréš îñ Çĥrömé šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_notice_sheet_opened_half">"Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx þrömþţ öþéñéð åţ ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_notice_sheet_opened_full">"Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx þrömþţ öþéñéð åţ ƒûļļ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_notice_sheet_closed_description">"Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx þrömþţ çļöšéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_notice_sheet_title">"Ĥéļþ ûš bûîļð å béţţér ŵéb - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_sandbox_notice_sheet_description">"Çĥrömé îš ƒîñðîñĝ ñéŵ ŵåýš ţö réðûçé ţråçķîñĝ åñð ķééþ ýöû évéñ šåƒér åš ýöû bröŵšé. Çĥrömé åļšö &lt;link&gt;éšţîmåţéš ýöûr îñţéréšţš&lt;/link&gt; åñð éñåbļéš ýöû ţö måñåĝé ţĥém. Ţĥéñ, šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ çåñ åšķ Çĥrömé ƒör ýöûr îñţéréšţš ţö šĥöŵ ýöû åðš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="settings_custom">"Çûšţöm - one"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dns_title">"Ûšé šéçûré ÐÑŠ - one two three"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dns_description">"Ðéţérmîñéš ĥöŵ ţö çöññéçţ ţö ŵébšîţéš övér å šéçûré çöññéçţîöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="settings_automatic_mode_label">"Ûšé ýöûr çûrréñţ šérvîçé þrövîðér - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="settings_automatic_mode_description">"Šéçûré ÐÑŠ måý ñöţ bé åvåîļåbļé åļļ ţĥé ţîmé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="settings_automatic_mode_summary">"Åûţömåţîç - one"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dropdown_mode_description">"Çĥööšé åñöţĥér þrövîðér - one two three"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dropdown_mode_privacy_policy">"Šéé ţĥîš þrövîðér\'š &lt;a target=\"_blank\" href=\"$1\"&gt;þrîvåçý þöļîçý&lt;/a&gt; - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dns_disabled_for_managed_environment">"Ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ îš ðîšåbļéð öñ måñåĝéð bröŵšérš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dns_disabled_for_parental_control">"Ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ îš ðîšåbļéð béçåûšé þåréñţåļ çöñţröļš åré öñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dns_custom_placeholder">"Þrövîðér Û®Ļ - one two"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dns_custom_format_error">"Éñţér å çörréçţļý ƒörmåţţéð Û®Ļ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="settings_secure_dns_custom_connection_error">"Þļéåšé vérîƒý ţĥåţ ţĥîš îš å våļîð þrövîðér ör ţrý åĝåîñ ļåţér - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_title">"Çļéår bröŵšîñĝ ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_summary">"Çļéår ĥîšţörý, çööķîéš, šîţé ðåţå, çåçĥé… - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_history_dialog_title">"Çļéåréð Çĥrömé ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_history_dialog_data_text">"Ţĥé šéļéçţéð ðåţå ĥåš bééñ rémövéð ƒröm Çĥrömé åñð ýöûr šýñçéð ðévîçéš.

Ýöûr Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ måý ĥåvé öţĥér ƒörmš öƒ bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý ļîķé šéårçĥéš åñð åçţîvîţý ƒröm öţĥér Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš åţ &lt;link&gt;mýåçţîvîţý.ĝööĝļé.çöm&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="clear_cache_title">"Çåçĥéð îmåĝéš åñð ƒîļéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="clear_history_title">"Bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_cookies_and_site_data_title">"Çööķîéš åñð šîţé ðåţå - one two three four"</string>
<string name="clear_cookies_and_site_data_summary_basic">"Šîĝñš ýöû öûţ öƒ möšţ šîţéš. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="clear_cookies_and_site_data_summary_basic_signed_in">"Šîĝñš ýöû öûţ öƒ möšţ šîţéš. Ýöû ŵöñ\'ţ bé šîĝñéð öûţ öƒ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_history_summary">"Çļéårš ĥîšţörý, îñçļûðîñĝ îñ ţĥé šéårçĥ böx. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_history_summary_synced_no_link">"Çļéårš ĥîšţörý ƒröm åļļ šýñçéð ðévîçéš. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="clear_search_history_link">"&lt;link1&gt;Šéårçĥ ĥîšţörý&lt;/link1&gt; åñð &lt;link2&gt;öţĥér ƒörmš öƒ åçţîvîţý&lt;/link2&gt; måý bé šåvéð îñ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ŵĥéñ ýöû’ré šîĝñéð îñ. Ýöû çåñ ðéļéţé ţĥém åñýţîmé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="clear_search_history_link_other_forms">"&lt;link1&gt;Öţĥér ƒörmš öƒ åçţîvîţý&lt;/link1&gt; måý bé šåvéð îñ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ŵĥéñ ýöû’ré šîĝñéð îñ. Ýöû çåñ ðéļéţé ţĥém åñýţîmé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="sign_out_of_chrome_link">"Ţö šîĝñ öûţ öƒ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ öñ åļļ ŵébšîţéš, &lt;link1&gt;šîĝñ öûţ öƒ Çĥrömé&lt;/link1&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="clear_search_history_non_google_dse">"Ýöûr šéårçĥ éñĝîñé îš %1$s. Šéé ţĥéîr îñšţrûçţîöñš ƒör ðéļéţîñĝ ýöûr šéårçĥ ĥîšţörý, îƒ åþþļîçåbļé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="clear_search_history_non_google_dse_unknown">"Šéé ýöûr šéårçĥ éñĝîñé’š îñšţrûçţîöñš ƒör ðéļéţîñĝ ýöûr šéårçĥ ĥîšţörý, îƒ åþþļîçåbļé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_passwords_title">"Šåvéð þåššŵörðš - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_form_data_title">"Åûţöƒîļļ ƒörm ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_progress_title">"Çļéårîñĝ bröŵšîñĝ ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_data_delete">"Çļéår ðåţå - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_progress_message">"Þļéåšé ŵåîţ… - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_title">"Ţîmé råñĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_hour">"Ļåšţ ĥöûr - one two"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_24_hours">"Ļåšţ 24 ĥöûrš - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_7_days">"Ļåšţ 7 ðåýš - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_four_weeks">"Ļåšţ 4 ŵééķš - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_everything">"Åļļ ţîmé - one two"</string>
<string name="important_sites_title">"Åļšö çļéår ðåţå ƒröm ţĥéšé šîţéš¿ - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="important_sites_title_with_app">"Åļšö çļéår ðåţå ƒröm ţĥéšé šîţéš &amp; åþþš¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_important_dialog_text">"Ţĥéšé šîţéš šéém îmþörţåñţ ţö ýöû: - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_important_dialog_text_with_app">"Ţĥéšé šîţéš åñð åþþš šéém îmþörţåñţ ţö ýöû: - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_important_dialog_button">"Çļéår - one"</string>
<string name="open_clear_browsing_data_dialog_button">"Çļéår bröŵšîñĝ ðåţå… - one two three"</string>
<string name="clear_browsing_data_basic_tab_title">"Båšîç - one"</string>
<string name="android_history_other_forms_of_history">"Ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ måý ĥåvé öţĥér ƒörmš öƒ bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý åţ &lt;link&gt;mýåçţîvîţý.ĝööĝļé.çöm&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="android_history_blocked_site">"Bļöçķéð šîţé - one two"</string>
<string name="multiple_history_items_deleted">"%1$s îţémš ðéļéţéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="prefs_privacy_guide_title">"Þrîvåçý ĝûîðé - one two"</string>
<string name="prefs_privacy_guide_summary">"®évîéŵ ķéý þrîvåçý åñð šéçûrîţý çöñţröļš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_welcome_title">"Å ĝûîðé öƒ ýöûr þrîvåçý çĥöîçéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_welcome_description">"Ţåķé å ĝûîðéð ţöûr öƒ ķéý þrîvåçý åñð šéçûrîţý çöñţröļš. För möré öþţîöñš, ĝö ţö îñðîvîðûåļ šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_start_button">"Ļéţ’š ĝö - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_when_on">"Ŵĥéñ öñ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_things_to_consider">"Ţĥîñĝš ţö çöñšîðér - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_msbb_item_one">"Ýöû’ļļ bröŵšé ƒåšţér béçåûšé çöñţéñţ îš þröåçţîvéļý ļöåðéð båšéð öñ ýöûr çûrréñţ ŵébþåĝé vîšîţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_msbb_item_two">"Ýöû’ļļ ĝéţ îmþrövéð šûĝĝéšţîöñš îñ ţĥé åððréšš bår - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_msbb_item_three">"Û®Ļš ýöû vîšîţ åré šéñţ ţö Ĝööĝļé ţö þréðîçţ ŵĥåţ šîţéš ýöû mîĝĥţ vîšîţ ñéxţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_msbb_item_four">"Îƒ ýöû åļšö šĥåré Çĥrömé ûšåĝé réþörţš, ţĥöšé réþörţš îñçļûðé ţĥé Û®Ļš ýöû vîšîţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sync_toggle">"Ĥîšţörý šýñç - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sync_item_one">"Ýöû’ļļ ĥåvé ýöûr ĥîšţörý öñ åļļ ýöûr šýñçéð ðévîçéš šö ýöû çåñ çöñţîñûé ŵĥåţ ýöû ŵéré ðöîñĝ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sync_item_two">"Îƒ Ĝööĝļé îš åļšö ýöûr ðéƒåûļţ šéårçĥ éñĝîñé, ýöû’ļļ šéé béţţér, çöñţéxţûåļļý réļévåñţ šûĝĝéšţîöñš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sync_item_three">"Ţĥé Û®Ļš ýöû vîšîţ åré šåvéð ţö ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_cookies_intro">"Çĥööšé ŵĥéñ ţö bļöçķ ţĥîrð-þårţý çööķîéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_cookies_block_incognito_title">"Bļöçķ ŵĥîļé ûšîñĝ îñçöĝñîţö - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_cookies_block_incognito_description">"Ŵĥîļé îñ îñçöĝñîţö, šîţéš çåñ’ţ ûšé ýöûr çööķîéš ţö šéé ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ åçţîvîţý åçröšš ðîƒƒéréñţ šîţéš, ƒör éxåmþļé, ţö þéršöñåļîžé åðš. Féåţûréš öñ šömé šîţéš måý bréåķ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_cookies_block_always_title">"Bļöçķ åļļ ţĥé ţîmé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_cookies_block_always_description">"Šîţéš çåñ öñļý ûšé ýöûr çööķîéš ţö šéé ýöûr bröŵšîñĝ åçţîvîţý öñļý öñ ţĥéîr öŵñ šîţé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_safe_browsing_intro">"Çĥööšé ýöûr Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ þröţéçţîöñ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_safe_browsing_enhanced_title">"Éñĥåñçéð þröţéçţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_safe_browsing_enhanced_description">"Fåšţér, þröåçţîvé þröţéçţîöñ åĝåîñšţ ðåñĝéröûš ŵébšîţéš, ðöŵñļöåðš, åñð éxţéñšîöñš - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_safe_browsing_standard_title">"Šţåñðårð þröţéçţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_safe_browsing_standard_description">"Šţåñðårð þröţéçţîöñ åĝåîñšţ ŵébšîţéš, ðöŵñļöåðš, åñð éxţéñšîöñš ţĥåţ åré ķñöŵñ ţö bé ðåñĝéröûš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_finish_button">"Fîñîšĥ - one"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_done_title">"®évîéŵ çömþļéţé¡ - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_done_description">"Éxþļöré möré šéţţîñĝš béļöŵ ör ƒîñîšĥ ñöŵ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_privacy_sandbox_heading">"Þrîvåçý Šåñðböx ţrîåļ - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_privacy_sandbox_description">"Šéé ĥöŵ Çĥrömé þļåñš ţö šåƒéĝûårð ýöû ƒröm çröšš-šîţé ţråçķîñĝ ŵĥîļé þréšérvîñĝ ţĥé öþéñ ŵéb - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_web_app_activity_heading">"Ŵéb &amp; Åþþ Åçţîvîţý - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_web_app_activity_description">"Çĥööšé ŵĥéţĥér ţö îñçļûðé Çĥrömé ĥîšţörý ƒör möré þéršöñåļîžéð éxþérîéñçéš îñ Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_explanation_content_description">"Þrîvåçý ĝûîðé éxþļåñåţîöñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_explanation_opened_half">"Þrîvåçý ĝûîðé éxþļåñåţîöñ öþéñéð åţ ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_explanation_opened_full">"Þrîvåçý ĝûîðé éxþļåñåţîöñ öþéñéð åţ ƒûļļ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_explanation_closed_description">"Þrîvåçý ĝûîðé éxþļåñåţîöñ çļöšéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_standard_item_one">"Ðéţéçţš åñð ŵårñš ýöû åböûţ ðåñĝéröûš évéñţš ŵĥéñ ţĥéý ĥåþþéñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_standard_item_two">"Çĥéçķš Û®Ļš ŵîţĥ å ļîšţ öƒ ûñšåƒé šîţéš šţöréð îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_standard_item_three">"Îƒ å šîţé ţrîéš ţö šţéåļ ýöûr þåššŵörð, ör ŵĥéñ ýöû ðöŵñļöåð å ĥårmƒûļ ƒîļé, Çĥrömé måý šéñð Û®Ļš îñçļûðîñĝ bîţš öƒ þåĝé çöñţéñţ ţö Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_enhanced_item_one">"Þréðîçţš åñð ŵårñš ýöû åböûţ ðåñĝéröûš évéñţš béƒöré ţĥéý ĥåþþéñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_enhanced_item_two">"Ķééþš ýöû šåƒé öñ Çĥrömé åñð måý bé ûšéð ţö îmþrövé ýöûr šéçûrîţý îñ öţĥér Ĝööĝļé åþþš ŵĥéñ ýöû åré šîĝñéð îñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_enhanced_item_three">"Îmþrövéš šéçûrîţý ƒör ýöû åñð évérýöñé öñ ţĥé ŵéb - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_enhanced_item_four">"Ŵårñš ýöû îƒ þåššŵörðš åré éxþöšéð îñ å ðåţå bréåçĥ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_enhanced_item_five">"Šéñðš Û®Ļš ţö Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ ţö çĥéçķ ţĥém - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_enhanced_item_six">"Åļšö šéñðš å šmåļļ šåmþļé öƒ þåĝéš, ðöŵñļöåðš, éxţéñšîöñ åçţîvîţý, åñð šýšţém îñƒörmåţîöñ ţö ĥéļþ ðîšçövér ñéŵ ţĥréåţš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="privacy_guide_sb_enhanced_item_seven">"Ţémþörårîļý ļîñķš ţĥîš ðåţå ţö ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ŵĥéñ ýöû’ré šîĝñéð îñ, ţö þröţéçţ ýöû åçröšš Ĝööĝļé åþþš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="prefs_safety_check">"Šåƒéţý çĥéçķ - one two"</string>
<string name="safety_check_description">"Çĥrömé çåñ ĥéļþ ķééþ ýöû šåƒé ƒröm ðåţå bréåçĥéš, ûñšåƒé ŵébšîţéš, åñð möré - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="safety_check_safe_browsing_title">"Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="safety_check_updates_title">"Ûþðåţéš - one"</string>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_title">"Þåššŵörðš - one"</string>
<string name="safety_check_button">"Çĥéçķ ñöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="safety_check_error">"Åñ érrör öççûrréð. - one two three"</string>
<string name="safety_check_safe_browsing_disabled">"Öƒƒ • Ñöţ réçömméñðéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="safety_check_safe_browsing_enabled_standard">"Šţåñðårð Þröţéçţîöñ îš öñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="safety_check_safe_browsing_enabled_enhanced">"Éñĥåñçéð Þröţéçţîöñ îš öñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="safety_check_safe_browsing_disabled_by_admin">"Ţûrñéð öƒƒ bý ýöûr åðmîñîšţråţör - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_safe">"Ñö çömþrömîšéð þåššŵörðš ƒöûñð - one two three four"</string>
<plurals name="safety_check_passwords_compromised_exist">
  <item quantity="one">"1 çömþrömîšéð þåššŵörð - one two three"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d çömþrömîšéð þåššŵörðš - one two three"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_no_passwords">"Ñö šåvéð þåššŵörðš - one two three"</string>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_error">"Çĥrömé çåñ’ţ çĥéçķ ýöûr þåššŵörðš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_error_offline">"Öƒƒļîñé. Çĥrömé çåñ’ţ çĥéçķ ýöûr þåššŵörðš. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_error_signed_out">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö ýöûr Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ ţö çĥéçķ ýöûr þåššŵörðš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_error_quota_limit">"Çĥrömé çöûļðñ’ţ çĥéçķ åļļ þåššŵörðš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="safety_check_passwords_update_play_services">"Ûþðåţé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šérvîçéš ţö çĥéçķ ýöûr þåššŵörðš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="safety_check_updates_updated">"Çĥrömé îš ûþ ţö ðåţé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="safety_check_updates_outdated">"Çĥrömé îš öûţ öƒ ðåţé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="safety_check_updates_offline">"Öƒƒļîñé. Çĥrömé çåñ’ţ çĥéçķ ƒör ûþðåţéš. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="safety_check_updates_error">"Çĥrömé çåñ’ţ çĥéçķ ƒör ûþðåţéš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="safety_check_timestamp_after">"Çĥéçķéð ĵûšţ ñöŵ - one two three"</string>
<plurals name="safety_check_timestamp_after_mins">
  <item quantity="one">"Çĥéçķéð 1 mîñûţé åĝö - one two three four"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"Çĥéçķéð %d mîñûţéš åĝö - one two three four"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="safety_check_timestamp_after_hours">
  <item quantity="one">"Çĥéçķéð 1 ĥöûr åĝö - one two three four"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"Çĥéçķéð %d ĥöûrš åĝö - one two three four"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="safety_check_timestamp_after_yesterday">"Çĥéçķéð ýéšţérðåý - one two"</string>
<plurals name="safety_check_timestamp_after_days">
  <item quantity="one">"Çĥéçķéð 1 ðåý åĝö - one two three four"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"Çĥéçķéð %d ðåýš åĝö - one two three four"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="prefs_safe_browsing_title">"Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="prefs_safe_browsing_summary">"%1$s îš öñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="prefs_safe_browsing_no_protection_summary">"Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ îš öƒƒ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="prefs_section_safe_browsing_title">"Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_title">"Éñĥåñçéð þröţéçţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_summary">"Fåšţér, þröåçţîvé þröţéçţîöñ åĝåîñšţ ðåñĝéröûš ŵébšîţéš, ðöŵñļöåðš, åñð éxţéñšîöñš. Ŵårñš ýöû åböûţ þåššŵörð bréåçĥéš. ®éqûîréš bröŵšîñĝ ðåţå ţö bé šéñţ ţö Ĝööĝļé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_standard_protection_title">"Šţåñðårð þröţéçţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_standard_protection_summary">"Šţåñðårð þröţéçţîöñ åĝåîñšţ ŵébšîţéš, ðöŵñļöåðš, åñð éxţéñšîöñš ţĥåţ åré ķñöŵñ ţö bé ðåñĝéröûš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_no_protection_title">"Ñö þröţéçţîöñ (ñöţ réçömméñðéð) - one two three four"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_no_protection_summary">"Ðöéš ñöţ þröţéçţ ýöû åĝåîñšţ ðåñĝéröûš ŵébšîţéš, ðöŵñļöåðš, åñð éxţéñšîöñš. Ýöû’ļļ šţîļļ ĝéţ Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ þröţéçţîöñ, ŵĥéré åvåîļåbļé, îñ öţĥér Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš, ļîķé Ĝmåîļ åñð Šéårçĥ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_subtitle">"Éñĥåñçéð þröţéçţîöñ: - one two"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_bullet_one">"Þréðîçţš åñð ŵårñš ýöû åböûţ ðåñĝéröûš évéñţš béƒöré ţĥéý ĥåþþéñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_bullet_two">"Ķééþš ýöû šåƒé öñ Çĥrömé åñð måý bé ûšéð ţö îmþrövé ýöûr šéçûrîţý îñ öţĥér Ĝööĝļé åþþš ŵĥéñ ýöû åré šîĝñéð îñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_bullet_three">"Îmþrövéš šéçûrîţý ƒör ýöû åñð évérýöñé öñ ţĥé ŵéb. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_bullet_four">"Ŵårñš ýöû îƒ þåššŵörðš åré éxþöšéð îñ å ðåţå bréåçĥ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_enhanced_protection_bullet_five">"Šéñðš Û®Ļš ţö Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ ţö çĥéçķ ţĥém. Åļšö šéñðš å šmåļļ šåmþļé öƒ þåĝéš, ðöŵñļöåðš, éxţéñšîöñ åçţîvîţý, åñð šýšţém îñƒörmåţîöñ ţö ĥéļþ ðîšçövér ñéŵ ţĥréåţš. Ţémþörårîļý ļîñķš ţĥîš ðåţå ţö ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ŵĥéñ ýöû’ré šîĝñéð îñ, ţö þröţéçţ ýöû åçröšš Ĝööĝļé åþþš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_standard_protection_subtitle">"Šţåñðårð þröţéçţîöñ: - one two"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_standard_protection_bullet_one">"Ðéţéçţš åñð ŵårñš ýöû åböûţ ðåñĝéröûš évéñţš ŵĥéñ ţĥéý ĥåþþéñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_standard_protection_bullet_two">"Çĥéçķš Û®Ļš ŵîţĥ å ļîšţ öƒ ûñšåƒé šîţéš šţöréð îñ Çĥrömé. Îƒ å šîţé ţrîéš ţö šţéåļ ýöûr þåššŵörð, ör ŵĥéñ ýöû ðöŵñļöåð å ĥårmƒûļ ƒîļé, Çĥrömé måý åļšö šéñð Û®Ļš, îñçļûðîñĝ bîţš öƒ þåĝé çöñţéñţ, ţö Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_standard_protection_extended_reporting_title">"Ĥéļþ îmþrövé šéçûrîţý öñ ţĥé ŵéb - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_standard_protection_extended_reporting_summary">"Šéñðš Û®Ļš öƒ šömé þåĝéš ýöû vîšîţ, ļîmîţéð šýšţém îñƒörmåţîöñ, åñð šömé þåĝé çöñţéñţ ţö Ĝööĝļé, ţö ĥéļþ ðîšçövér ñéŵ ţĥréåţš åñð þröţéçţ évérýöñé öñ ţĥé ŵéb. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_no_protection_confirmation_dialog_title">"Ţûrñ öƒƒ Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_no_protection_confirmation_dialog_message">"Šåƒé Bröŵšîñĝ þröţéçţš ýöû åĝåîñšţ ðéçéþţîvé ŵébšîţéš. Îƒ ýöû ţûrñ îţ öƒƒ, bé éxţrå çåréƒûļ ŵĥéñ bröŵšîñĝ, éšþéçîåļļý béƒöré éñţérîñĝ þåššŵörðš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="safe_browsing_no_protection_confirmation_dialog_confirm">"Ţûrñ öƒƒ - one two"</string>
<string name="language_settings">"Ļåñĝûåĝéš - one"</string>
<string name="app_language_title">"%1$s’š ļåñĝûåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="default_lang_subtitle">"Çûrréñţ ðévîçé ļåñĝûåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="add_language">"Åðð ļåñĝûåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="change_chrome_lang">"Çĥåñĝé ļåñĝûåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_select">"Šéļéçţ ļåñĝûåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_select_suggested">"Šûĝĝéšţéð ļåñĝûåĝéš - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_select_other">"Öţĥér ļåñĝûåĝéš - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_content_title">"Þréƒérréð ļåñĝûåĝéš - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_content_description">"Ţö šĥöŵ çöñţéñţ îñ ýöûr þréƒérréð ļåñĝûåĝéš, ţĥé šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ çåñ šéé ýöûr þréƒéréñçéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="languages_list_description">"Ŵébšîţéš ŵîļļ šĥöŵ ţéxţ îñ ýöûr þréƒérréð ļåñĝûåĝé, ŵĥéñ þöššîbļé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="languages_offer_translate_switch">"Öƒƒér ţö ţråñšļåţé þåĝéš îñ öţĥér ļåñĝûåĝéš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="languages_send_translate_switch">"Öƒƒér ţö šéñð þåĝéš îñ öţĥér ļåñĝûåĝéš ţö Ĝööĝļé Ţråñšļåţé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="languages_item_option_offer_to_translate">"Öƒƒér ţö ţråñšļåţé - one two three"</string>
<string name="languages_explicit_ask_title">"Ŵĥåţ ļåñĝûåĝéš ðö ýöû réåð¿ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="languages_srp_title">"Þîçķ Çĥrömé’š ļåñĝûåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="languages_srp_subtitle">"Ýöûr ķéýböårð ŵöñ’ţ çĥåñĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="languages_more_languages">"Möré ļåñĝûåĝéš - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_srp_loading_text">"Ļöåðîñĝ %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_split_downloading">"%1$s - Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ… - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_split_ready">"%1$s - Ļåñĝûåĝé réåðý, réšţårţ %2$s. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="languages_split_failed">"%1$s - Ţĥîš ļåñĝûåĝé çöûļðñ\'ţ bé ðöŵñļöåðéð. Ţrý åĝåîñ ļåţér. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="languages_infobar_ready">"%1$s îš réåðý - one two three"</string>
<string name="languages_infobar_restart">"®éšţårţ Çĥrömé - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_translation_title">"Ţråñšļåţîöñ šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_advanced">"Åðvåñçéð - one"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_target">"Ţråñšļåţé îñţö ţĥîš ļåñĝûåĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_automatic">"Åûţömåţîçåļļý ţråñšļåţé ţĥéšé ļåñĝûåĝéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_automatic_title">"Åûţömåţîçåļļý ţråñšļåţé - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_dont_offer_langs">"Ðöñ’ţ öƒƒér ţö ţråñšļåţé ţĥéšé ļåñĝûåĝéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_never_langs_title">"Ñévér ţråñšļåţé - one two"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_dont_offer_sites">"Ðöñ’ţ öƒƒér ţö ţråñšļåţé ţĥéšé šîţéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="languages_settings_never_sites_title">"Ñévér ţråñšļåţé šîţéš - one two three"</string>
<string name="dangerous_download_dialog_confirm_text">"Ðöŵñļöåð åñýŵåý - one two"</string>
<string name="dangerous_download_dialog_text">"Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö ðöŵñļöåð %1$s åñýŵåý¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="dangerous_download_dialog_text_with_size">"Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö ðöŵñļöåð %1$s (%2$s) åñýŵåý¿ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="dangerous_download_dialog_title">"Fîļé mîĝĥţ bé ĥårmƒûļ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="mixed_content_download_dialog_title">"Fîļé çåñ’ţ bé ðöŵñļöåðéð šéçûréļý - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="mixed_content_download_dialog_confirm_text">"Ķééþ - one"</string>
<string name="mixed_content_download_dialog_discard_text">"Ðîšçårð - one"</string>
<string name="download_date_time_picker_next_text">"Ñéxţ - one"</string>
<string name="download_later_prompt_enabled_title">"Åšķ ŵĥéñ ţö šåvé ƒîļéš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="downloads_location_selector_title">"Ðöŵñļöåð ļöçåţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="downloads_location_sd_card">"ŠÐ Çårð - one two"</string>
<string name="downloads_location_sd_card_number">"ŠÐ Çårð %1$d - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_location_prompt_enabled_title">"Åšķ ŵĥéré ţö šåvé ƒîļéš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="download_location_dialog_title">"Çĥööšé ŵĥéré ţö ðöŵñļöåð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_location_dialog_title_confirm_download">"Ðöŵñļöåð ƒîļé¿ - one two"</string>
<string name="download_location_dialog_checkbox">"Ðöñ‘ţ šĥöŵ åĝåîñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_location_download_again">"Ðöŵñļöåð ƒîļé åĝåîñ¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_location_name_exists">"Fîļé ñåmé åļréåðý éxîšţš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_location_rename_file">"®éñåmé ƒîļé - one two"</string>
<string name="download_location_name_too_long">"Fîļé ñåmé ţöö ļöñĝ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_location_not_enough_space">"Ñöţ éñöûĝĥ šþåçé - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_location_download_to_default_folder">"Ðöŵñļöåð ţö ðéƒåûļţ ƒöļðér¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_location_no_sd_card">"ŠÐ çårð ñöţ ƒöûñð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_location_no_sd_card_snackbar">"ŠÐ çårð ñöţ ƒöûñð. Šömé öƒ ýöûr ƒîļéš måý bé mîššîñĝ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="download_location_no_available_locations">"Ñö åvåîļåbļé ðöŵñļöåð ļöçåţîöñš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_location_incognito_warning">"Åñýöñé ûšîñĝ ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ šéé ðöŵñļöåðéð ƒîļéš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="rename">"®éñåmé - one"</string>
<string name="rename_failure_name_conflict">"Ñåmé åļréåðý éxîšţš - one two three"</string>
<string name="rename_failure_name_too_long">"Ñåmé îš ţöö ļöñĝ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="rename_failure_name_invalid">"Ñåmé îš îñvåļîð - one two three"</string>
<string name="rename_failure_unavailable">"®éñåmé ûñåvåîļåbļé - one two"</string>
<string name="rename_extension_confirmation">"Çĥåñĝé ƒîļé éxţéñšîöñ¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="rename_extension_message">"Îƒ ýöû çĥåñĝé ţĥé ƒîļé éxţéñšîöñ, ţĥé ƒîļé måý öþéñ îñ å ðîƒƒéréñţ åþþļîçåţîöñ åñð þöţéñţîåļļý bé å ĥåžårð ţö ýöûr ðévîçé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="duplicate_download_dialog_confirm_text">"Ðöŵñļöåð åĝåîñ - one two"</string>
<string name="duplicate_download_dialog_text">"Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö ðöŵñļöåð ^1^2 åĝåîñ¿ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="duplicate_download_dialog_title">"Ðöŵñļöåð ƒîļé åĝåîñ¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="duplicate_page_download_dialog_title">"Ðöŵñļöåð þåĝé åĝåîñ¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="prefs_about_chrome">"Åböûţ Çĥrömé - one two"</string>
<string name="legal_information_summary">"Çöþýrîĝĥţ %1$d Ĝööĝļé ĻĻÇ. Åļļ rîĝĥţš réšérvéð. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="application_version_title">"Åþþļîçåţîöñ véršîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="version_with_update_time">"%1$s (Ûþðåţéð %2$s) - one two three"</string>
<string name="os_version_title">"Öþéråţîñĝ šýšţém - one two"</string>
<string name="deprecation_warning">"Çĥrömé ûþðåţéš åré ñö ļöñĝér šûþþörţéð ƒör ţĥîš véršîöñ öƒ Åñðröîð - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="account_management_title">"Šîĝñéð îñ ţö Ĝööĝļé åš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="account_management_sign_out">"Šîĝñ öûţ öƒ Çĥrömé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="account_management_parental_settings">"Þåréñţåļ Šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="account_management_no_parental_data">"Ŵåîţîñĝ ƒör ðéţåîļš öƒ þåréñţš. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="account_management_one_parent_name">"Ţĥîš bröŵšér îš måñåĝéð bý %1$s. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="account_management_two_parent_names">"Ţĥîš bröŵšér îš måñåĝéð bý %1$s åñð %2$s. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="account_management_child_content_title">"Çöñţéñţ - one"</string>
<string name="account_management_child_content_approved">"Öñļý åļļöŵ çérţåîñ šîţéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="account_management_child_content_filter_mature">"Ţrý ţö bļöçķ måţûré šîţéš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="account_management_child_content_all">"Åļļöŵ åļļ šîţéš - one two three"</string>
<string name="parent_website_approval_title">"%1$s wants you to approve this website:"</string>
<string name="parent_website_approval_all_of_domain">"All pages of %1$s"</string>
<string name="parent_website_approval_approve_button">"Approve"</string>
<string name="parent_website_approval_deny_button">"Don’t approve"</string>
<string name="parent_website_approval_content_description">"Option to approve or not approve a website"</string>
<string name="parent_website_approval_full_height">"Option to approve or not approve a website opened at full height"</string>
<string name="parent_website_approval_closed">"Option to approve or not approve a website closed"</string>
<string name="sync_on">"Öñ - one"</string>
<string name="sync_off">"Öƒƒ - one"</string>
<string name="sync_data_types_off">"Ñö ðåţå šéļéçţéð ţö šýñç - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_settings_not_confirmed">"Ţåþ ţö šéţ ûþ šýñç - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_is_disabled_by_administrator">"Šýñç îš ðîšåbļéð bý ýöûr åðmîñîšţråţör - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="sync_need_passphrase">"Þåššþĥråšé réqûîréð - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_setup_progress">"Šéţûþ îñ þröĝréšš… - one two three"</string>
<string name="legal_information_title">"Ļéĝåļ îñƒörmåţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="open_source_license_title">"Öþéñ šöûrçé ļîçéñšéš - one two three"</string>
<string name="open_source_license_url">"chrome://credits"</string>
<string name="google_terms_of_service_title">"Ĝööĝļé Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="google_terms_of_service_url">"https://policies.google.com/terms/embedded"</string>
<string name="google_terms_of_service_dark_mode_url">"https://policies.google.com/terms/embedded?color_scheme=dark"</string>
<string name="chrome_additional_terms_of_service_title">"Çĥrömé &amp; ÇĥröméÖŠ Åððîţîöñåļ Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="chrome_additional_terms_of_service_url">"https://www.google.com/chrome/terms/"</string>
<string name="privacy_policy_title">"Ĝööĝļé Þrîvåçý Þöļîçý - one two three"</string>
<string name="google_privacy_policy_url">"https://policies.google.com/privacy"</string>
<string name="signout_title">"Šîĝñ öûţ öƒ Çĥrömé¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="turn_off_sync_and_signout_title">"Šîĝñ öûţ åñð ţûrñ öƒƒ šýñç¿ - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="turn_off_sync_title">"Ţûrñ öƒƒ šýñç¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="signout_managed_account_title">"Çļéår ýöûr Çĥrömé ðåţå ƒröm ţĥîš ðévîçé¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="signout_message">"Šömé Çĥrömé ƒéåţûréš ŵöñ\û2019ţ bé åvåîļåbļé åñýmöré - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="turn_off_sync_and_signout_message">"Ýöûr bööķmårķš, ĥîšţörý, þåššŵörðš, åñð öţĥér Çĥrömé ðåţå ŵîļļ ñö ļöñĝér bé šýñçéð ţö ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="remove_local_data">"Åļšö çļéår ýöûr Çĥrömé ðåţå ƒröm ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="signout_managed_account_message">"Béçåûšé ýöû\'ré šîĝñîñĝ öûţ öƒ åñ åççöûñţ måñåĝéð bý %1$s, ýöûr Çĥrömé ðåţå ŵîļļ bé ðéļéţéð ƒröm ţĥîš ðévîçé. Îţ ŵîļļ rémåîñ îñ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="sign_in_getting_account_management_policy">"Çöñţåçţîñĝ Ĝööĝļé. Ţĥîš måý ţåķé å mîñûţé… - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sign_in_timeout_title">"Çåñ’ţ šîĝñ îñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="sign_in_timeout_message">"Ĝööĝļé ţööķ ţöö ļöñĝ ţö réšþöñð - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="sign_in_managed_account">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö måñåĝéð åççöûñţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sign_in_managed_account_description">"Ýöû åré šîĝñîñĝ îñ ŵîţĥ åñ åççöûñţ måñåĝéð bý %1$s åñð ĝîvîñĝ îţš åðmîñîšţråţör çöñţröļ övér ýöûr Çĥrömé ðåţå. Ýöûr ðåţå ŵîļļ béçömé þérmåñéñţļý ţîéð ţö ţĥîš åççöûñţ. Šîĝñîñĝ öûţ öƒ Çĥrömé ŵîļļ ðéļéţé ýöûr ðåţå ƒröm ţĥîš ðévîçé, bûţ îţ ŵîļļ rémåîñ šţöréð îñ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="sync_your_bookmarks">"Šýñç ýöûr bööķmårķš - one two three"</string>
<string name="enable_sync_button">"Öþéñ šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="open_settings_button">"Öþéñ šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmarks_sync_promo_enable_sync">"Bööķmårķš šåvéð öñ ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_sync_promo_enable_chrome_sync">"Ţö ĝéţ ýöûr ţåbš ƒröm ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš, ţûrñ öñ šýñç. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="ntp_recent_tabs_sync_promo_instructions">"Ţåbš ţĥåţ ýöû\'vé öþéñéð îñ Çĥrömé öñ ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="search_and_browse_category">"Šéårçĥ åñð bröŵšé - one two three"</string>
<string name="syncing_category">"Šýñçîñĝ - one"</string>
<string name="sync_everything_pref">"Šýñç évérýţĥîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_autofill">"Åððréššéš åñð möré - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_bookmarks">"Bööķmårķš - one"</string>
<string name="sync_history">"Ĥîšţörý - one"</string>
<string name="sync_passwords">"Þåššŵörðš - one"</string>
<string name="sync_reading_list">"®éåðîñĝ ļîšţ - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_recent_tabs">"Öþéñ ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_settings">"Šéţţîñĝš - one"</string>
<string name="sync_payments_integration">"Þåýméñţ méţĥöðš, öƒƒérš, åñð åððréššéš ûšîñĝ Ĝööĝļé Þåý - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="sync_encryption">"Éñçrýþţîöñ - one"</string>
<string name="sync_review_data">"®évîéŵ ýöûr šýñçéð ðåţå - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_type_title">"Éñçrýþţîöñ - one"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_type_keystore">"Éñçrýþţ šýñçéð þåššŵörðš ŵîţĥ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_type_custom">"Éñçrýþţ šýñçéð ðåţå ŵîţĥ ýöûr öŵñ šýñç þåššþĥråšé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_type_custom_dialog_title">"Çréåţé þåššþĥråšé - one two"</string>
<string name="sign_in_google_account">"Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_custom_passphrase">"Þåššþĥråšé éñçrýþţîöñ ðöéšñ’ţ îñçļûðé þåýméñţ méţĥöðš åñð åððréššéš ƒröm Ĝööĝļé Þåý. Öñļý šöméöñé ŵîţĥ ýöûr þåššþĥråšé çåñ réåð ýöûr éñçrýþţéð ðåţå. Ţĥé þåššþĥråšé îš ñöţ šéñţ ţö ör šţöréð bý Ĝööĝļé. Îƒ ýöû ƒörĝéţ ýöûr þåššþĥråšé ör ŵåñţ ţö çĥåñĝé ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ ýöû\'ļļ ñééð ţö réšéţ šýñç. &lt;learnmore&gt;Ļéårñ möré&lt;/learnmore&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="sync_enter_custom_passphrase_hint">"Þåššþĥråšé - one"</string>
<string name="sync_enter_custom_passphrase_hint_confirm">"Çöñƒîrm þåššþĥråšé - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_enter_passphrase_body_with_date_android">"Ýöûr ðåţå ŵåš éñçrýþţéð ŵîţĥ ýöûr &lt;learnmore&gt;šýñç þåššþĥråšé&lt;/learnmore&gt; öñ %1$s. Éñţér îţ ţö šţårţ šýñç. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sync_account_info">"Šîĝñéð îñ åš %1$s. - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_cannot_be_blank">"Ţĥîš ƒîéļð çåññöţ bé bļåñķ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_reset_instructions">"Îƒ ýöû ƒörĝöţ ýöûr þåššþĥråšé ör ŵåñţ ţö çĥåñĝé ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ, &lt;resetlink&gt;réšéţ šýñç&lt;/resetlink&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrases_do_not_match">"Þåššþĥråšéš ðö ñöţ måţçĥ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_encryption_reset_instructions">"Þåššþĥråšé éñçrýþţîöñ ðöéšñ’ţ îñçļûðé þåýméñţ méţĥöðš åñð åððréššéš ƒröm Ĝööĝļé Þåý.

Ţö çĥåñĝé ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ, &lt;resetlink&gt;réšéţ šýñç&lt;/resetlink&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="sync_passphrase_incorrect">"Îñçörréçţ þåššþĥråšé - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_verifying">"Vérîƒýîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="sync_loading">"Ļöåðîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="sync_import_data_prompt">"Ýöû ĥåvé bööķmårķš, ĥîšţörý, þåššŵörðš, åñð öţĥér šéţţîñĝš ƒröm %1$s. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="sync_import_existing_data">"Çömbîñé mý ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_import_existing_data_subtext">"Åðð éxîšţîñĝ ðåţå ţö %1$s. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_keep_existing_data_separate">"Ķééþ mý ðåţå šéþåråţé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_keep_existing_data_separate_subtext_existing_data">"Ðéļéţé éxîšţîñĝ ðåţå. - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_error_card_title">"Šýñç îšñ\'ţ ŵörķîñĝ - one two three"</string>
<string name="password_sync_error_summary">"Þåššŵörð šýñç îšñ\'ţ ŵörķîñĝ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_settings_not_confirmed_title">"Îñîţîåļ šýñç šéţûþ ñöţ ƒîñîšĥéð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_needs_verification_title">"Šýñç ñééðš ţö vérîƒý îţ\'š ýöû - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="hint_sync_auth_error">"Šîĝñ îñ åĝåîñ ţö šţårţ šýñç - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="hint_sync_recoverability_degraded_for_everything">"Måķé šûré ýöû çåñ åļŵåýš åççéšš ýöûr šýñç ðåţå - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="hint_sync_recoverability_degraded_for_passwords">"Måķé šûré ýöû çåñ åļŵåýš åççéšš ýöûr šåvéð þåššŵörðš - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="hint_sync_retrieve_keys_for_everything">"Ţö šţårţ šýñç, vérîƒý îţ\'š ýöû - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="hint_sync_retrieve_keys_for_passwords">"Ţö šýñç ýöûr þåššŵörðš, vérîƒý îţ\'š ýöû - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="hint_passphrase_required">"Ţö šţårţ šýñç, éñţér ýöûr þåššþĥråšé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="hint_sync_settings_not_confirmed_description">"Çĥööšé ŵĥåţ ţö šýñç béļöŵ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="hint_other_sync_errors">"Ţrý šîĝñîñĝ îñ åĝåîñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="hint_client_out_of_date">"Ûþðåţé %1$s ţö šţårţ šýñç - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="client_out_of_date_error_card_button">"Ûþðåţé %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="passphrase_required_error_card_button">"Éñţér þåššþĥråšé - one two"</string>
<string name="auth_error_card_button">"Šîĝñ îñ åĝåîñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="trusted_vault_error_card_button">"Vérîƒý îţ\'š ýöû - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_error_generic">"Šýñç ĥåš šţöþþéð ŵörķîñĝ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_error_ga">"Þļéåšé ûþðåţé ýöûr šîĝñ-îñ ðéţåîļš. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_error_connection">"Çöûļð ñöţ çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé šýñç šérvér. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sync_error_upgrade_client">"%1$s îš öûţ öƒ ðåţé. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sync_error_service_unavailable">"Ţĥé šérvîçé îš ñöţ åvåîļåbļé; ţrý åĝåîñ ļåţér. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="policy_dialog_proceed">"Åççéþţ åñð šîĝñ îñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="wiping_profile_data_title">"Çļéårîñĝ åççöûñţ ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="wiping_profile_data_message">"Þļéåšé ŵåîţ… - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_standard_stack">"Šţåñðårð ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_incognito_stack">"Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_standard_stack_selected">"Šŵîţçĥéð ţö šţåñðårð ţåbš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_incognito_stack_selected">"Šŵîţçĥéð ţö Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_undo_tab_closed">"®éöþéñ çļöšéð ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_undo_closed_tab_announcement_message">"®éšţöréð %1$s, ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_undo_multiple_closed_tabs_announcement_message">"®éšţöréð %1$s ţåbš - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab">"%1$s, ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_selected">"%1$s, ţåb, šéļéçţéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_btn_close_tab">"Çļöšé %1$s ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="tab_loading_default_title">"Ļöåðîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="top_bar_screen_position">"Öþţîöñš åvåîļåbļé ñéår ţöþ öƒ ţĥé šçrééñ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="duplicate_download_infobar_text">"Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö ðöŵñļöåð ^1 åĝåîñ¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="duplicate_download_request_infobar_text">"Ðö ýöû ŵåñţ ţö šţårţ ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ ^1 åĝåîñ¿ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="duplicate_download_infobar_download_button">"Ðöŵñļöåð - one"</string>
<string name="download_message_download_in_progress_description">"Šéé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñ ƒör ðöŵñļöåð šţåţûš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="download_message_download_complete_description">"(%1$s) %2$s - one two"</string>
<plurals name="download_message_multiple_download_in_progress">
  <item quantity="one">"Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ ƒîļé… - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ %d ƒîļéš… - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="download_message_multiple_download_complete">
  <item quantity="one">"Fîļé ðöŵñļöåðéð - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ðöŵñļöåðš çömþļéţé - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="download_message_multiple_download_failed">
  <item quantity="one">"1 ðöŵñļöåð ƒåîļéð - one two three"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ðöŵñļöåðš ƒåîļéð - one two three"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="download_message_multiple_download_pending">
  <item quantity="one">"1 ðöŵñļöåð þéñðîñĝ - one two three"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ðöŵñļöåðš þéñðîñĝ - one two three"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="download_message_multiple_download_scheduled">
  <item quantity="one">"1 ðöŵñļöåð šçĥéðûļéð - one two three"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ðöŵñļöåðš šçĥéðûļéð - one two three"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="download_message_download_scheduled_description_on_wifi">"Ðöŵñļöåð ŵîļļ šţårţ ŵĥéñ öñ Ŵî-Fî - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="download_message_download_scheduled_description_on_date">"Ðöŵñļöåð ŵîļļ šţårţ öñ %1$s. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="download_message_download_scheduled_description_on_time">"Ðöŵñļöåð ŵîļļ šţårţ åţ %1$s. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="incognito_download_message_title">"Ðöŵñļöåð ƒîļé¿ - one two"</string>
<string name="incognito_download_message_detail">"Åñýöñé ûšîñĝ ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ šéé ðöŵñļöåðéð ƒîļéš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="incognito_download_message_button">"Ðöŵñļöåð - one"</string>
<string name="menu_translate">"Ţråñšļåţé… - one"</string>
<string name="menu_print">"Þrîñţ… - one"</string>
<string name="menu_share_page">"Šĥåré… - one"</string>
<string name="accessibility_menu_share_via">"Šĥåré vîå %s - one two three"</string>
<string name="error_printing_failed">"Ţĥéré ŵåš å þröbļém þrîñţîñĝ ţĥé þåĝé. Þļéåšé ţrý åĝåîñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="accessibility_menu_bookmark">"Bööķmårķ ţĥîš þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_menu_forward">"Ĝö ƒörŵårð - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_menu_info">"Vîéŵ šîţé îñƒörmåţîöñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_content_view">"Ŵéb Vîéŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="password_generation_dialog_title">"Šûĝĝéšţéð þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_generation_dialog_title_upm_branded">"Ûšé šţröñĝ þåššŵörð¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="password_generation_dialog_cancel_button">"Çåñçéļ - one"</string>
<string name="password_generation_dialog_use_password_button">"Ûšé þåššŵörð - one two"</string>
<string name="password_filling_reauth_prompt_title">"Vérîƒý îţ’š ýöû - one two three"</string>
<string name="password_manager_outdated_gms_dialog_description">"Ţö måñåĝé ýöûr þåššŵörðš, ûþðåţé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šérvîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="password_manager_outdated_gms_positive_button">"Ûþðåţé - one"</string>
<string name="password_manager_outdated_gms_negative_button">"Ñöţ ñöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="missing_storage_permission_download_education_text">"Çĥrömé ñééðš šţöråĝé åççéšš ţö ðöŵñļöåð ƒîļéš. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_other_window">"Öþéñ îñ öţĥér ŵîñðöŵ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_new_window">"Öþéñ îñ ñéŵ ŵîñðöŵ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_new_tab">"Öþéñ îñ ñéŵ ţåb - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_new_tab_group">"Öþéñ îñ ñéŵ ţåb îñ ĝröûþ - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_incognito_tab">"Öþéñ îñ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_call">"Çåļļ - one"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_copy">"Çöþý - one"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_send_message">"Šéñð méššåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_add_to_contacts">"Åðð ţö çöñţåçţš - one two three"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_copy_link_address">"Çöþý ļîñķ åððréšš - one two three"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_copy_link_text">"Çöþý ļîñķ ţéxţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_save_link">"Ðöŵñļöåð ļîñķ - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_save_image">"Ðöŵñļöåð îmåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_image">"Öþéñ îmåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_image_in_new_tab">"Öþéñ îmåĝé îñ ñéŵ ţåb - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_image_in_ephemeral_tab">"Þrévîéŵ îmåĝé &lt;new&gt;Ñéŵ&lt;/new&gt; - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_load_original_image">"Ļöåð îmåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_copy_image">"Çöþý îmåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_search_image_with_google_lens">"Šéårçĥ îmåĝé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Ļéñš &lt;new&gt;Ñéŵ&lt;/new&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_translate_image_with_google_lens">"Ţråñšļåţé îmåĝé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Ļéñš &lt;new&gt;Ñéŵ&lt;/new&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_shop_image_with_google_lens">"Šĥöþ îmåĝé ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Ļéñš &lt;new&gt;Ñéŵ&lt;/new&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_search_web_for_image">"Šéårçĥ %1$s ƒör ţĥîš îmåĝé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_share_image">"Šĥåré îmåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_share_link">"Šĥåré ļîñķ - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_save_video">"Ðöŵñļöåð vîðéö - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_new_chrome_tab">"Öþéñ îñ ñéŵ Çĥrömé ţåb - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_chrome_incognito_tab">"Öþéñ îñ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_open_in_ephemeral_tab">"Þrévîéŵ þåĝé &lt;new&gt;Ñéŵ&lt;/new&gt; - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_read_later">"Åðð ţö réåðîñĝ ļîšţ &lt;new&gt;Ñéŵ&lt;/new&gt; - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_performance_info_fast">"Fåšţ þåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_share_highlight">"Šĥåré ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_remove_highlight">"®émövé ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ - one two"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_learn_more">"Ļéårñ möré… - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_swipe_refresh">"®éƒréšĥîñĝ þåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="dark_mode">"Ðårķ - one"</string>
<string name="light_mode">"Ļîĝĥţ - one"</string>
<string name="sepia_mode">"Šéþîå - one"</string>
<string name="sans_serif">"Šåñš Šérîƒ - one two"</string>
<string name="serif">"Šérîƒ - one"</string>
<string name="monospace">"Möñöšþåçé - one"</string>
<string name="text_size_signifier">"Å - one"</string>
<string name="menu_open_webapk">"Öþéñ %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="open_webapk_failed">"Çöûļð ñöţ öþéñ åþþ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="app_banner_add">"Åðð - one"</string>
<string name="notification_webapk_install_in_progress">"Åððîñĝ %1$s… - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_webapk_installed">"Åððéð ţö Ĥömé šçrééñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="iph_pwa_install_available_text">"Îñšţåļļ ţĥîš åþþ - one two three"</string>
<string name="iph_message_add_to_home_screen_title">"Åðð ţö Ĥömé šçrééñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="iph_message_add_to_home_screen_description">"Ĝéţ ţö ţĥîš šîţé qûîçķér ñéxţ ţîmé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="iph_message_add_to_home_screen_action">"Åðð - one"</string>
<string name="iph_message_shared_highlighting_title">"Çréåţé å ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţéð ļîñķ ļîķé ţĥîš öñé¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="iph_message_shared_highlighting_button">"Ļéårñ Möré - one two"</string>
<string name="page_info_connection_offline">"Ýöû åré vîéŵîñĝ åñ öƒƒļîñé çöþý öƒ ţĥîš þåĝé ƒröm %1$s - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="page_info_offline_page_not_trusted_with_date">"Ţĥîš öƒƒļîñé þåĝé îš ƒröm %1$s åñð måý ðîƒƒér ƒröm ţĥé öñļîñé véršîöñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="page_info_offline_page_not_trusted_without_date">"Ţĥîš þåĝé måý ðîƒƒér ƒröm ţĥé öñļîñé véršîöñ. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="page_info_connection_paint_preview">"Ýöû åré vîéŵîñĝ å þrévîéŵ öƒ ţĥîš þåĝé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="page_info_iph">"Çĥåñĝé ýöûr šîţé šéţţîñĝš ĥéré - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sad_tab_suggestions">"Îƒ ýöû’ré šééîñĝ ţĥîš ƒréqûéñţļý, ţrý ţĥéšé &lt;link&gt;šûĝĝéšţîöñš&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="notification_hidden_text">"Çöñţéñţš ĥîððéñ - one two"</string>
<string name="notification_site_settings_button">"Šéţţîñĝš - one"</string>
<string name="notification_manage_button">"Måñåĝé - one"</string>
<string name="notification_work_profile_badge_content_description">"Ŵörķ þröƒîļé - one two"</string>
<string name="download_notification_pending">"Ðöŵñļöåð þéñðîñĝ… - one two"</string>
<string name="download_notification_pending_network">"Ŵåîţîñĝ ƒör ñéţŵörķ… - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_notification_pending_another_download">"Ŵåîţîñĝ ƒör åñöţĥér ðöŵñļöåð… - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_notification_incognito_subtext">"Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="download_cant_open_file">"Çåñ’ţ öþéñ ƒîļé - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_failed_reason_file_already_exists">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåð þrévéñţéð béçåûšé ƒîļé åļréåðý éxîšţš. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="download_failed_reason_file_system_error">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåð ƒåîļéð ðûé ţö ƒîļé šýšţém érrörš. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="download_failed_reason_insufficient_space">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåð ƒåîļéð ðûé ţö ļåçķ öƒ šţöråĝé šþåçé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="download_failed_reason_network_failures">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåð ƒåîļéð ðûé ţö ñéţŵörķ ƒåîļûréš. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="download_failed_reason_server_issues">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåð ƒåîļéð ðûé ţö šérvér îššûéš. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="download_failed_reason_storage_not_found">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåð ƒåîļéð béçåûšé šţöråĝé ļöçåţîöñ îš ñöţ réåçĥåbļé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="download_failed_reason_unknown_error">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåð ƒåîļéð ðûé ţö åñ ûñķñöŵñ érrör. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="download_started">"Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="one_file_left">"1 ƒîļé ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="files_left">"%1$d ƒîļéš ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<plurals name="download_ui_files_downloaded">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$d ƒîļé ðöŵñļöåðéð - one two three"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$d ƒîļéš ðöŵñļöåðéð - one two three"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="remaining_duration_days">"%1$d ðåýš ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="remaining_duration_one_day">"1 ðåý ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="remaining_duration_hours">"%1$d ĥöûrš ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="remaining_duration_one_hour">"1 ĥöûr ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="remaining_duration_minutes">"%1$d mîñš ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="remaining_duration_one_minute">"1 mîñ ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="remaining_duration_seconds">"%1$d šéçš ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="remaining_duration_one_second">"1 šéç ļéƒţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="proceed_oma_download_message">"Þröçééð ţö ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé çöñţéñţ¿ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="open_url_post_oma_download">"Öþéñ ţĥé šûĝĝéšţéð Û®Ļ šþéçîƒîéð îñ ţĥé ðöŵñļöåðéð çöñţéñţ¿ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="oma_download_insufficient_memory">"Îñšûƒƒîçîéñţ mémörý ţö ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé šéļéçţéð çöñţéñţ. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="oma_download_non_acceptable_content">"Ðévîçé çåññöţ öþéñ ţĥé çöñţéñţ ţö bé ðöŵñļöåðéð. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="oma_download_failed">"Åñ érrör öççûrréð ŵĥîļé ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ ţĥé çöñţéñţ. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="oma_download_name_label">"Ñåmé: - one"</string>
<string name="oma_download_vendor_label">"Véñðör: - one"</string>
<string name="oma_download_size_label">"Šîžé: - one"</string>
<string name="oma_download_type_label">"Ţýþé: - one"</string>
<string name="oma_download_description_label">"Ðéšçrîþţîöñ: - one"</string>
<string name="open_downloaded_label">"Öþéñ - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_space_free_kb">"%1$3.2f ĶB åvåîļåbļé - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_space_free_mb">"%1$3.2f MB åvåîļåbļé - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_space_free_gb">"%1$3.2f ĜB åvåîļåbļé - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_space_using">"Ûšîñĝ %1$s öƒ %2$s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_all_downloads">"Åļļ - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_pages">"Þåĝéš - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_video">"Vîðéö - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_audio">"Åûðîö - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_images">"Îmåĝéš - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_card_pagination">"Šéé möré - one two"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_list_pagination">"Möré - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_documents">"Ðöçûméñţš - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_ui_other">"Öţĥér - one"</string>
<plurals name="accessibility_download_manager_ui_generic">
  <item quantity="one">"%d Fîļé - one"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d Fîļéš - one"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="accessibility_download_manager_ui_images">
  <item quantity="one">"%d Îmåĝé - one"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d Îmåĝéš - one"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="accessibility_download_manager_ui_video">
  <item quantity="one">"%d Vîðéö - one"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d Vîðéöš - one"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="accessibility_download_manager_ui_audio">
  <item quantity="one">"%d Åûðîö ƒîļé - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d Åûðîö ƒîļéš - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="accessibility_download_manager_ui_pages">
  <item quantity="one">"%d Þåĝé - one"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d Þåĝéš - one"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="download_page">"Ðöŵñļöåð þåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="download_manager_no_downloads">"Fîļéš ţĥåţ ýöû ðöŵñļöåð åþþéår ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="download_manager_open_with">"Öþéñ ŵîţĥ… - one two"</string>
<string name="download_manager_search">"Šéårçĥ ýöûr ðöŵñļöåðš - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_list_item_description">"%1$s • %2$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_list_item_description_no_size">"%1$s - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_files_tab">"Mý Fîļéš - one two"</string>
<string name="download_manager_prefetch_caption">"%1$s • %2$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_prefetch_tab_empty">"Årţîçļéš åþþéår ĥéré, ŵĥîçĥ ýöû çåñ réåð évéñ ŵĥéñ ýöû\'ré öƒƒļîñé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<plurals name="download_manager_n_hours">
  <item quantity="one">"%d ĥr - one"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ĥrš - one"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="download_manager_paused">"þåûšéð - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_pending">"þéñðîñĝ - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_failed">"ƒåîļéð - one"</string>
<string name="download_manager_in_progress_description">"%1$s • %2$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_just_now">"Ĵûšţ ñöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="download_manager_scheduled_later">"Šçĥéðûļéð ƒör ļåţér - one two three"</string>
<string name="download_manager_offline_home">"Öƒƒļîñé Ĥömé - one two"</string>
<string name="download_manager_explore_offline">"Éxþļöré Öƒƒļîñé - one two"</string>
<string name="history_manager_empty">"Þåĝéš ţĥåţ ýöû vîšîţ åþþéår ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="history_manager_no_results">"Çåñ’ţ ƒîñð ţĥåţ þåĝé. Çĥéçķ ýöûr šþéļļîñĝ ör ţrý å šéårçĥ öñ %1$s. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="history_manager_no_results_no_dse">"Çåñ’ţ ƒîñð ţĥåţ þåĝé. Çĥéçķ ýöûr šþéļļîñĝ ör ţrý å ŵéb šéårçĥ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="history_manager_search">"Šéårçĥ ýöûr ĥîšţörý - one two three"</string>
<string name="incognito_history_placeholder_title">"Šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ åréñ’ţ šåvéð îñ Îñçöĝñîţö - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="incognito_history_placeholder_description">"Ţö çļéår Îñçöĝñîţö bröŵšîñĝ ĥîšţörý ƒröm ýöûr ðévîçé, çļöšé åļļ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="close_all_incognito_notification_title">"Îñçöĝñîţö Ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="close_all_incognito_notification">"Çļöšé åļļ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="incognito_reauth_page_unlock_incognito_button_label">"Ûñļöçķ Îñçöĝñîţö - one two"</string>
<string name="incognito_reauth_page_see_other_tabs_label">"Šéé öţĥér ţåbš - one two three"</string>
<string name="incognito_reauth_promo_title">"Ļöçķ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš ŵĥéñ ýöû ļéåvé Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="incognito_reauth_promo_description">"Ûšé šçrééñ ļöçķ ţö šéé öþéñ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="incognito_reauth_lock_action_text">"Ţûrñ öñ Îñçöĝñîţö ļöçķ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="incognito_reauth_snackbar_text">"Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš ŵîļļ bé ļöçķéð ŵĥéñ ýöû ļéåvé Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="card_unmask_input_hint">"ÇVÇ - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_expiration_date_month_hint">"MM - one"</string>
<string name="autofill_expiration_date_year_hint">"ÝÝ - one"</string>
<string name="fre_activity_label">"Çĥrömé Fîršţ ®ûñ Éxþérîéñçé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="fre_tos">"Bý ûšîñĝ Çĥrömé, ýöû åĝréé ţö ţĥé &lt;TOS_LINK&gt;Ĝööĝļé Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/TOS_LINK&gt;, åñð ţĥé &lt;ATOS_LINK&gt;Ĝööĝļé Çĥrömé åñð ÇĥröméÖŠ Åððîţîöñåļ Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/ATOS_LINK&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="fre_tos_and_privacy_child_account">"Bý ûšîñĝ Çĥrömé, ýöû åĝréé ţö ţĥé &lt;TOS_LINK&gt;Ĝööĝļé Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/TOS_LINK&gt;, åñð ţĥé &lt;ATOS_LINK&gt;Ĝööĝļé Çĥrömé åñð ÇĥröméÖŠ Åððîţîöñåļ Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/ATOS_LINK&gt;. Ţĥé &lt;PRIVACY_LINK&gt;Þrîvåçý Þöļîçý&lt;/PRIVACY_LINK&gt; åļšö åþþļîéš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_fre_associated_app_tos">"%1$s ŵîļļ öþéñ îñ Çĥrömé. Bý çöñţîñûîñĝ, ýöû åĝréé ţö ţĥé &lt;LINK1&gt;Ĝööĝļé Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/LINK1&gt;, åñð ţĥé &lt;LINK2&gt;Ĝööĝļé Çĥrömé åñð ÇĥröméÖŠ Åððîţîöñåļ Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/LINK2&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="lightweight_fre_associated_app_tos_and_privacy_child_account">"%1$s ŵîļļ öþéñ îñ Çĥrömé. Bý çöñţîñûîñĝ, ýöû åĝréé ţö ţĥé &lt;LINK1&gt;Ĝööĝļé Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/LINK1&gt;, åñð ţĥé &lt;LINK2&gt;Ĝööĝļé Çĥrömé åñð ÇĥröméÖŠ Åððîţîöñåļ Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/LINK2&gt;. Ţĥé &lt;LINK3&gt;Þrîvåçý Þöļîçý&lt;/LINK3&gt; åļšö åþþļîéš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="fre_send_report_check">"Ĥéļþ måķé Çĥrömé béţţér bý šéñðîñĝ ûšåĝé šţåţîšţîçš åñð çråšĥ réþörţš ţö Ĝööĝļé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="fre_accept_continue">"Åççéþţ &amp; çöñţîñûé - one two"</string>
<string name="fre_welcome">"Ŵéļçömé ţö Çĥrömé - one two three"</string>
<string name="fre_browser_managed_by_organization">"Ýöûr bröŵšér îš måñåĝéð bý ýöûr örĝåñîžåţîöñ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_dismiss_button">"Ûšé ŵîţĥöûţ åñ åççöûñţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_footer">"Bý çöñţîñûîñĝ, ýöû åĝréé ţö ţĥé &lt;TOS_LINK&gt;Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/TOS_LINK&gt;.\ñŢö ĥéļþ îmþrövé ţĥé åþþ, Çĥrömé šéñðš ûšåĝé åñð çråšĥ ðåţå ţö Ĝööĝļé. &lt;UMA_LINK&gt;Måñåĝé&lt;/UMA_LINK&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_footer_tos">"Bý çöñţîñûîñĝ, ýöû åĝréé ţö ţĥé &lt;TOS_LINK&gt;Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/TOS_LINK&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_footer_tos_with_supervised_user">"Bý çöñţîñûîñĝ, ýöû åĝréé ţö ţĥé &lt;TOS_LINK&gt;Ţérmš öƒ Šérvîçé&lt;/TOS_LINK&gt; åñð &lt;PRIVACY_LINK&gt;Þrîvåçý\û00Å0Þöļîçý&lt;/PRIVACY_LINK&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_footer_metrics_reporting">"Ţö ĥéļþ îmþrövé ţĥé åþþ, Çĥrömé šéñðš ûšåĝé åñð çråšĥ ðåţå ţö Ĝööĝļé. &lt;UMA_LINK&gt;Måñåĝé&lt;/UMA_LINK&gt; - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_uma_dialog_title">"Måķé Çĥrömé béţţér - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_uma_dialog_first_section_header">"Ŵĥéñ öñ - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_uma_dialog_first_section_body">"Ĥéļþ måķé Çĥrömé béţţér ƒör þéöþļé ŵĥö ûšé îţ ţĥé ŵåý ýöû ðö - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_uma_dialog_second_section_header">"Ţĥîñĝš ţö çöñšîðér - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_uma_dialog_second_section_body">"Îñƒö îš šéñţ ţö Ĝööĝļé åböûţ ýöûr Çĥrömé ûšåĝé, bûţ îţ îšñ\û2019ţ ţîéð ţö ýöû\ñ\ñÎƒ Çĥrömé çråšĥéš, ðéţåîļš åböûţ ţĥé çråšĥ måý îñçļûðé šömé þéršöñåļ îñƒö\ñ\ñÎƒ ýöû ţûrñ öñ šýñç, méţrîçš måý åļšö îñçļûðé îñƒö åböûţ Û®Ļš ýöû vîšîţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_subtitle_variation_1">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö ĝéţ ţĥé möšţ öûţ öƒ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_subtitle_variation_2">"Šîĝñ îñ ƒör åððîţîöñåļ ƒéåţûréš åñð Çĥrömé\û2019š šţröñĝéšţ šéçûrîţý - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_subtitle_variation_3">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö bröŵšé éåšîér åçröšš ðévîçéš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_title_variation_1">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö ĝéţ ţĥé möšţ öûţ öƒ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_fre_title_variation_2">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö måķé Çĥrömé ýöûr öŵñ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="fre_signing_in">"Šîĝñîñĝ îñ\û2026 - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_add_account">"Åðð åççöûñţ - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_add_account_to_device">"Åðð åççöûñţ ţö ðévîçé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="signin_title">"Ţûrñ öñ šýñç¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_consent_title">"Ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_consent_subtitle">"Båçķ ûþ ýöûr šţûƒƒ åñð ûšé îţ öñ åñý ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="signin_sync_title">"Šýñç ýöûr þåššŵörðš, ĥîšţörý &amp; möré öñ åļļ ðévîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="signin_sync_description">"Ĝööĝļé måý ûšé ýöûr ĥîšţörý ţö þéršöñåļîžé Šéårçĥ åñð öţĥér Ĝööĝļé šérvîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_details_description">"Ýöû çåñ åļŵåýš çĥööšé ŵĥåţ ţö šýñç îñ &lt;LINK1&gt;šéţţîñĝš&lt;/LINK1&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="sync_consent_details_description">"Ýöû çåñ åļŵåýš çĥööšé ŵĥåţ ţö šýñç îñ &lt;LINK1&gt;šéţţîñĝš&lt;/LINK1&gt;. Ĝööĝļé måý þéršöñåļîžé Šéårçĥ åñð öţĥér šérvîçéš båšéð öñ ýöûr ĥîšţörý. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_consent_bookmarks_text">"Bööķmårķš - one"</string>
<string name="sync_consent_autofill_text">"Åûţöƒîļļ - one"</string>
<string name="sync_consent_history_text">"Ĥîšţörý åñð möré - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_accept_button">"Ýéš, Î\'m îñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_dialog_title">"Çĥööšé åñ åççöûñţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_bottom_sheet_title_for_send_tab_to_self">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="account_picker_bottom_sheet_accessibility_opened">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé, öþéñéð. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="account_picker_bottom_sheet_accessibility_closed">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé, çļöšéð. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_bottom_sheet_subtitle">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö ţĥîš šîţé åñð Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_bottom_sheet_subtitle_for_send_tab_to_self">"Ţö šéñð ţĥîš ţåb ţö åñöţĥér ðévîçé, šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé öñ böţĥ ðévîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_bottom_sheet_signin_title">"Šîĝñîñĝ îñ… - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_bottom_sheet_error_title">"Çåñ\'ţ šîĝñ îñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_general_error_subtitle">"Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ ðûrîñĝ šîĝñ-îñ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_auth_error_subtitle">"Ýöûr šţöréð šîĝñ-îñ îñƒö mîĝĥţ bé öûţ öƒ ðåţé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_dismiss_button">"Šķîþ - one"</string>
<string name="signin_account_picker_general_error_button">"Ţrý åĝåîñ - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_continue_as">"Çöñţîñûé åš %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_choose_account">"Ñöţ %1$s¿ - one two"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_title_bookmarks">"Ĝéţ åļļ ýöûr bööķmårķš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_description_bookmarks">"Šýñç ţö ĝéţ ýöûr bööķmårķš ƒröm ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_bookmarks">"Ţö ĝéţ ýöûr bööķmårķš öñ åļļ ýöûr ðévîçéš, ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_bookmarks_no_account">"Ţö ĝéţ ýöûr bööķmårķš öñ åļļ ýöûr ðévîçéš, šîĝñ îñ åñð ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_title_ntp_content_suggestions">"Šéé çöñţéñţ ƒör ýöû - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_alternative_title_ntp_content_suggestions">"Ĝéţ béţţér šûĝĝéšţîöñš - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_description_ntp_content_suggestions">"Šýñç ţö ĝéţ ţĥé möšţ réļévåñţ çöñţéñţ ƒröm Ĝööĝļé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_ntp_content_suggestions">"Ţö ĝéţ þéršöñåļîžéð çöñţéñţ šûĝĝéšţéð bý Ĝööĝļé, ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_ntp_content_suggestions_no_account">"Ţö ĝéţ þéršöñåļîžéð çöñţéñţ šûĝĝéšţéð bý Ĝööĝļé, šîĝñ îñ åñð ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_title_recent_tabs">"Çöñţîñûé ƒröm åñöţĥér ðévîçé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_alternative_title_recent_tabs">"Ĝéţ åļļ ýöûr ţåbš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_description_recent_tabs">"Šýñç ţö ĝéţ ýöûr ţåbš ƒröm ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_recent_tabs">"Ţö ĝéţ ýöûr ţåbš ƒröm ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš, ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_recent_tabs_no_account">"Ţö ĝéţ ýöûr ţåbš ƒröm ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš, šîĝñ îñ åñð ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_title_settings">"Bröŵšé möré éåšîļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_alternative_title_settings">"Ûšé Çĥrömé ýöûr ŵåý - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_description_settings">"Šýñç ţö ĝéţ ýöûr þåššŵörðš, bööķmårķš åñð möré öñ ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_settings">"Ţö šýñç åñð þéršöñåļîžé åçröšš ðévîçéš, ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_description_settings_no_account">"Ţö šýñç åñð þéršöñåļîžé åçröšš ðévîçéš, šîĝñ îñ åñð ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="signin_promo_choose_another_account">"Çĥööšé åñöţĥér åççöûñţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_turn_on_sync">"Ţûrñ öñ šýñç - one two three"</string>
<string name="sync_promo_continue">"Çöñţîñûé - one"</string>
<string name="external_app_restricted_access_error">"Çĥrömé ðöéš ñöţ ĥåvé åççéšš ţö ţĥé réqûéšţéð réšöûrçé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="new_tab_title">"Ñéŵ ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="new_incognito_tab_title">"Ñéŵ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs">"®éçéñţ ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="most_visited_placeholder_title">"Ñöţĥîñĝ ţö šéé ĥéré… ýéţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="most_visited_placeholder_summary">"Ýöûr möšţ vîšîţéð þåĝéš ŵîļļ åþþéår ĥéré - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="most_visited_item_removed">"Îţém rémövéð - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_google_doodle">"Ĝööĝļé ðööðļé: %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="ntp_recent_tabs_sync_promo_title">"Öţĥér ðévîçéš - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_recent_tabs_last_synced">"Ļåšţ šýñçéð: %1$s - one two three"</string>
<plurals name="n_minutes_ago">
  <item quantity="one">"%d mîñûţé åĝö - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d mîñûţéš åĝö - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="n_hours_ago">
  <item quantity="one">"%d ĥöûr åĝö - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ĥöûrš åĝö - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="n_days_ago">
  <item quantity="one">"%d ðåý åĝö - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ðåýš åĝö - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="just_now">"ĵûšţ ñöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_open_all_menu_option">"Öþéñ åļļ - one two"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_hide_menu_option">"Ĥîðé ƒör ñöŵ - one two three"</string>
<string name="recently_closed">"®éçéñţļý çļöšéð - one two"</string>
<string name="show_full_history">"Šĥöŵ ƒûļļ ĥîšţörý - one two three"</string>
<string name="remove_all">"®émövé åļļ - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_learn_more_about_suggested_content">"&lt;link&gt;Ļéårñ möré&lt;/link&gt; åböûţ šûĝĝéšţéð çöñţéñţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="ntp_manage_my_activity">"Måñåĝé åçţîvîţý - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_manage_interests">"Måñåĝé îñţéréšţš - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_manage_reactions">"Måñåĝé réåçţîöñš - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_manage_autoplay">"Måñåĝé åûţöþļåý - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_manage_feed">"Måñåĝé - one"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_activity">"Åçţîvîţý - one"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_activity_description">"Çöñţröļ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ðåţå - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_interests">"Îñţéréšţš - one"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_interests_description">"Måñåĝé ţĥé ţöþîçš ýöû\'ré îñţéréšţéð îñ - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_hidden">"Ĥîððéñ - one"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_hidden_description">"Ĥîðé åñð ûñĥîðé ţöþîçš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_autoplay">"Åûţöþļåý - one"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_autoplay_description">"Måñåĝé Vîðéö Þrévîéŵ Šéţţîñĝš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_following">"Föļļöŵîñĝ - one"</string>
<string name="feed_manage_following_description">"Måñåĝé ţĥé šîţéš ýöû ƒöļļöŵ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="follow_manage_following">"Föļļöŵîñĝ - one"</string>
<string name="follow_manage_following_empty_state">"Ýöû\'ļļ ƒîñð šîţéš ýöû ƒöļļöŵ ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="follow_manage_updates_unavailable">"Ûþðåţéš Ûñåvåîļåbļé - one two"</string>
<string name="follow_manage_waiting_for_content">"Ŵåîţîñĝ ƒör çöñţéñţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="feed_follow_unknown_error">"Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. Ţrý åĝåîñ ļåţér. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="feed_follow_no_connection_error">"Ñö çöññéçţîöñ. Ţrý åĝåîñ ļåţér. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="ntp_turn_off_feed">"Ţûrñ öƒƒ - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_turn_on_feed">"Ţûrñ öñ - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_discover_on">"Ðîšçövér - one"</string>
<string name="ntp_discover_on_branded">"Ðîšçövér bý Ĝööĝļé - one two three"</string>
<string name="ntp_discover_off">"Ðîšçövér - öƒƒ - one two"</string>
<string name="ntp_discover_off_branded">"Ðîšçövér bý Ĝööĝļé - öƒƒ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="ntp_following">"Föļļöŵîñĝ - one"</string>
<string name="ntp_feed_menu_iph">"Çöñţröļ ýöûr šţörîéš åñð åçţîvîţý ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="accessibility_ntp_feed_menu_button">"Öþţîöñš ƒör Ðîšçövér - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_ntp_feed_menu_iph">"Çöñţröļ ýöûr šţörîéš ƒröm ţĥé Öþţîöñš ƒör Ðîšçövér bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="accessibility_ntp_following_unread_content">"Ûñréåð šţörîéš réåðý - one two three"</string>
<string name="feed_options_dropdown_description">"Öþéñ šörţ öþţîöñš - one two three"</string>
<string name="feed_options_dropdown_description_close">"Çļöšé šörţ öþţîöñš - one two three"</string>
<string name="feed_options_sort_by_grouped">"Šörţ bý Šîţé - one two three"</string>
<string name="feed_options_sort_by_latest">"Šörţ bý Ļåţéšţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="feed_sort_publisher">"Šîţé - one"</string>
<string name="discover_no_cards">"Ñö šţörîéš åvåîļåbļé - one two three"</string>
<string name="discover_no_cards_instructions">"Çĥéçķ båçķ ļåţér ƒör ñéŵ šţörîéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="discover_cant_refresh">"Çåñ\'ţ réƒréšĥ Ðîšçövér - one two three"</string>
<string name="discover_cant_refresh_instructions">"Çĥéçķ båçķ ļåţér ƒör ñéŵ šţörîéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="web_feed_no_cards_title">"Ķééþ ûþ ŵîţĥ ýöûr ƒåvörîţé šîţéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="web_feed_no_cards_instructions">"Ţö ƒöļļöŵ å šîţé, ĝö ţö ţĥé šîţé, öþéñ ţĥé Çĥrömé méñû, åñð ţåþ Föļļöŵ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="feed_swipe_refresh_iph">"För ñéŵ šţörîéš, þûļļ ðöŵñ ţö réƒréšĥ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="accessibility_feed_swipe_refresh_iph">"Ţö réƒréšĥ ţĥé ƒééð çöñţéñţ, þûļļ ðöŵñ ţĥé þåĝé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="feed_back_to_top_prompt">"Båçķ ţö ţöþ - one two three"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_bulk_closure">"%1$s ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_group_closure_with_title">"Ţåb ĝröûþ - %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_group_closure_without_title">"Ţåb ĝröûþ - %1$s ţåbš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_bulk_closure_accessibility">"®éšţöré %1$s ţåbš åš ñéŵ båçķĝröûñð ţåbš. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_group_closure_with_title_accessibility">"®éšţöré ţåb ĝröûþ %1$s åš å ñéŵ båçķĝröûñð ţåb ĝröûþ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="recent_tabs_group_closure_without_title_accessibility">"®éšţöré ţåb ĝröûþ öƒ %1$s ţåbš åš å ñéŵ båçķĝröûñð ţåb ĝröûþ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="web_feed_awareness">"Föļļöŵ åñý šîţéš ýöû ŵåñţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_title">"Éxþļöré - one"</string>
<string name="ntp_explore_sites_more">"Möré çåţéĝörîéš - one two"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_loading_from_net">"Fîñðîñĝ ţĥé béšţ ƒröm ţĥé ŵéb… - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_loading_error">"Çåñ\'ţ ļöåð ţĥîš þåĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_loading_error_next_steps_tag">"Ţrý: - one"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_loading_error_next_steps_reload">"®éļöåðîñĝ ţĥé þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_loading_error_next_steps_check_connection">"Çĥéçķîñĝ ýöûr îñţérñéţ çöññéçţîöñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_iph">"Šéé þöþûļår ŵébšîţéš - one two three"</string>
<string name="explore_sites_iph_accessibility">"Šéé þöþûļår ŵébšîţéš bý ţåþþîñĝ ţĥé \"Ţöþ šîţéš\" bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_card_chrome_intro">"Ĥöŵ ţö ûšé Çĥrömé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_card_search">"Ĥöŵ ţö šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ Çĥrömé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_card_voice_search">"Ĥöŵ ţö šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ ýöûr vöîçé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_card_download">"Ĥöŵ ţö ðöŵñļöåð çöñţéñţ ƒör ļåţér - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_card_all_videos">"Vîðéöš åböûţ ĥöŵ ţö ûšé Çĥrömé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_learn_chrome">"Ļéårñ Çĥrömé - one two"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_popular_videos">"Þöþûļår vîðéöš - one two"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_tile_chrome_intro">"Ñåvîĝåţé Çĥrömé - one two"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_tile_search">"Šéårçĥ ţĥé îñţérñéţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_tile_voice_search">"Ûšé vöîçé šéårçĥ - one two three"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_tile_download">"Ðöŵñļöåð çöñţéñţ - one two"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_language_picker_title">"Þîçķ ýöûr ļåñĝûåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_watch">"Ŵåţçĥ - one"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_try_now">"Ţrý ñöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_watch_next_video">"Ŵåţçĥ ñéxţ vîðéö - one two three"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_change_language">"Çĥåñĝé %1$s¿ - one two"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_accessibility_share">"Šĥåré - one"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_accessibility_close">"Çļöšé - one"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_iph_tap_here_to_start">"Ţåþ ĥéré ţö šţårţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_iph_tap_voice_icon_to_start">"Ţýþé ĥéré ör ţåþ ţĥé vöîçé îçöñ ţö šţårţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="video_tutorials_loading">"Ļöåðîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_notification_title">"Çĥrömé ţîþš - one two"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_notification_message_default_browser">"Ļéårñ ĥöŵ ţö šéţ Çĥrömé åš ýöûr ðéƒåûļţ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_notification_message_sign_in">"Ţö ĝéţ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé šţûƒƒ åçröšš ðévîçéš, šîĝñ îñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_notification_message_incognito_tab">"Ţö bröŵšé þrîvåţéļý öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé, ţrý öûţ Îñçöĝñîţö - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_notification_message_ntp_suggestion_card">"Ðîšçövér ñéŵ çöñţéñţ öñ Çĥrömé’š ĥöméþåĝé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_notification_message_voice_search">"Ýöû çåñ ûšé ýöûr vöîçé ţö šéårçĥ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_tooltip_message_incognito_tab">"Ţö öþéñ å ñéŵ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb, öþéñ ţĥé méñû - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_tooltip_message_ntp_suggestion_card">"Šçröļļ ðöŵñ ţö šéé šûĝĝéšţéð årţîçļéš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_tooltip_message_voice_search">"Ţö šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ ýöûr vöîçé, ţåþ ţĥé mîçröþĥöñé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="feature_notification_guide_tooltip_message_sign_in">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé ŵîţĥ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="open_tabs">"Öþéñ ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="button_new_tab">"Ñéŵ ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="button_new_incognito_tab">"Ñéŵ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="custom_tab_amp_publisher_url">"Fröm &lt;pub&gt;%1$s&lt;/pub&gt; – &lt;bg&gt;ðéļîvéréð bý Ĝööĝļé&lt;/bg&gt; - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_new_tab">"Ñéŵ ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_share">"Šĥåré - one"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_voice_search">"Vöîçé šéårçĥ - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_based_on_your_usage">"Båšéð öñ ýöûr ûšåĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_based_on_your_usage_description">"Çûrréñţ réçömméñðåţîöñ:  %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="toolbar_shortcut">"Ţööļbår šĥörţçûţ - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_new_tab_iph">"Qûîçķļý öþéñ å ñéŵ ţåb. Ţö éðîţ ţĥîš šĥörţçûţ, ţöûçĥ åñð ĥöļð. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_share_iph">"Qûîçķļý šĥåré ţĥîš þåĝé. Ţö éðîţ ţĥîš šĥörţçûţ, ţöûçĥ åñð ĥöļð. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_voice_search_iph">"Qûîçķļý šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ ýöûr vöîçé. Ţö éðîţ ţĥîš šĥörţçûţ, ţöûçĥ åñð ĥöļð. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_new_tab_iph_settings">"Qûîçķļý öþéñ å ñéŵ ţåb. Ţö éðîţ ţĥîš šĥörţçûţ, ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_share_iph_settings">"Qûîçķļý šĥåré ţĥîš þåĝé. Ţö éðîţ ţĥîš šĥörţçûţ, ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_voice_search_iph_settings">"Qûîçķļý šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ ýöûr vöîçé. Ţö éðîţ ţĥîš šĥörţçûţ, ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_menu_edit_shortcut">"Éðîţ šĥörţçûţ - one two"</string>
<string name="adaptive_toolbar_edit_shortcut">"Éðîţ ţööļbår šĥörţçûţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_update">"Ûþðåţé Çĥrömé - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_update_summary_default">"Ñéŵér véršîöñ îš åvåîļåbļé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="menu_update_unsupported">"Çĥrömé çåñ’ţ ûþðåţé - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_update_unsupported_summary_default">"Åñðröîð véršîöñ îš ûñšûþþörţéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="menu_new_window">"Ñéŵ ŵîñðöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_move_to_other_window">"Mövé ţö öţĥér ŵîñðöŵ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="menu_manage_all_windows">"Måñåĝé ŵîñðöŵš (%1$d) - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_forward">"Förŵårð - one"</string>
<string name="menu_bookmark">"Bööķmårķ - one"</string>
<string name="menu_download">"Ðöŵñļöåð - one"</string>
<string name="menu_page_info">"Þåĝé îñƒö - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_stop_refresh">"Šţöþ réƒréšĥîñĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_new_tab">"Ñéŵ ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_new_incognito_tab">"Ñéŵ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_bookmarks">"Bööķmårķš - one"</string>
<string name="menu_recent_tabs">"®éçéñţ ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_history">"Ĥîšţörý - one"</string>
<string name="menu_downloads">"Ðöŵñļöåðš - one"</string>
<string name="menu_add_bookmark">"Bööķmårķ - one"</string>
<string name="menu_edit_bookmark">"Éðîţ Bööķmårķ - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_add_to_reading_list">"Åðð ţö réåðîñĝ ļîšţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="menu_delete_from_reading_list">"Ðéļéţé ƒröm réåðîñĝ ļîšţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="menu_find_in_page">"Fîñð îñ þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_follow">"Föļļöŵ - one"</string>
<string name="menu_following">"Föļļöŵîñĝ - one"</string>
<string name="follow_accelerator">"Föļļöŵ ţĥîš šîţé ĥéré - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_follow_accelerator_iph">"Åððš ţĥé çûrréñţ ŵéb šîţé ţö ţĥé ļîšţ öƒ ŵéb šîţéš ţĥåţ ýöû åré ƒöļļöŵîñĝ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="menu_item_request_desktop_site">"®éqûéšţ ðéšķţöþ šîţé - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_item_request_mobile_site">"®éqûéšţ möbîļé šîţé - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_paint_preview_show">"Show Paint Preview"</string>
<string name="menu_request_desktop_site">"Ðéšķţöþ šîţé - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_request_desktop_site_on">"Ţûrñ öƒƒ ®éqûéšţ ðéšķţöþ šîţé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="menu_request_desktop_site_off">"Ţûrñ öñ ®éqûéšţ ðéšķţöþ šîţé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="menu_auto_dark_web_contents">"Ðårķ ţĥémé - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_reader_mode_prefs">"Åþþéåråñçé - one"</string>
<string name="menu_settings">"Šéţţîñĝš - one"</string>
<string name="menu_close_all_tabs">"Çļöšé åļļ ţåbš - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_close_all_incognito_tabs">"Çļöšé Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_group_tabs">"Ĝröûþ ţåbš - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_track_prices">"Ţråçķ þrîçéš - one two"</string>
<string name="menu_get_image_descriptions">"Ĝéţ îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_stop_image_descriptions">"Šţöþ îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš - one two three"</string>
<string name="bookmarks">"Bööķmårķš - one"</string>
<string name="bookmarks_folder_empty">"Þåĝéš ţĥåţ ýöû bööķmårķ åþþéår ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="no_bookmarks">"Ñö bööķmårķš - one two"</string>
<plurals name="bookmarks_count">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$d bööķmårķ - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$d bööķmårķš - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="bookmark_page_saved">"Bööķmårķéð îñ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="bookmark_page_saved_default">"Bööķmårķéð - one"</string>
<string name="bookmark_page_saved_folder">"Bööķmårķéð ţö %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="bookmark_page_failed">"Fåîļéð ţö åðð bööķmårķ. - one two three four"</string>
<string name="bookmark_parent_folder">"Þåréñţ ƒöļðér - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_item_select">"Šéļéçţ - one"</string>
<string name="bookmark_item_edit">"Éðîţ - one"</string>
<string name="bookmark_item_move">"Mövé ţö… - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_item_delete">"Ðéļéţé - one"</string>
<string name="bookmark_show_in_folder">"Šĥöŵ îñ ƒöļðér - one two three"</string>
<string name="bookmark_add_folder">"Ñéŵ ƒöļðér… - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_choose_folder">"Çĥööšé ƒöļðér - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_action_bar_edit_folder">"Éðîţ ƒöļðér - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_action_bar_move">"Mövé bööķmårķš - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_action_bar_delete">"Ðéļéţé bööķmårķš - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_action_bar_close">"Çļöšé ðîåļöĝ - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_action_bar_search">"Šéårçĥ ýöûr bööķmårķš - one two three"</string>
<string name="bookmark_no_result">"Çåñ’ţ ƒîñð ţĥåţ bööķmårķ. Çĥéçķ ýöûr šþéļļîñĝ ör åðð å ñéŵ bööķmårķ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="edit_bookmark">"Éðîţ bööķmårķ - one two"</string>
<string name="add_folder">"Åðð ƒöļðér - one two"</string>
<string name="edit_folder">"Éðîţ ƒöļðér - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_name">"Ñåmé - one"</string>
<string name="bookmark_url">"Û®Ļ - one"</string>
<string name="bookmark_folder">"Föļðér - one"</string>
<string name="bookmark_missing_title">"Ţîţļé réqûîréð - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_missing_url">"Û®Ļ réqûîréð - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmarks_save_flow_content_description">"Bööķmårķ šåvé ƒļöŵ - one two three"</string>
<string name="bookmarks_save_flow_opened_half">"Bööķmårķ šåvé ƒļöŵ öþéñéð åţ ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="bookmarks_save_flow_opened_full">"Bööķmårķ šåvé ƒļöŵ ƒöļðérš öþéñéð åţ ƒûļļ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="bookmarks_save_flow_closed_description">"Bööķmårķ šåvé ƒļöŵ çļöšéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="bookmark_page_saved_location">"îñ %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_page_moved_location">"ţö %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_save_flow_title">"Bööķmårķ šåvéð - one two"</string>
<string name="bookmark_save_flow_title_move">"Bööķmårķ mövéð - one two"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_title">"Ţråçķîñĝ þrîçé - one two"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_save_flow_notification_switch_subtitle">"Ĝéţ åļérţš îƒ ţĥé þrîçé ðröþš öñ åñý šîţé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_save_flow_notification_switch_subtitle_error">"Çöûļðñ’ţ ûþðåţé Ţråçķ þrîçé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="enable_price_tracking_menu_item">"Ţråçķ þrîçé - one two"</string>
<string name="disable_price_tracking_menu_item">"Šţöþ ţråçķîñĝ þrîçé - one two three"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_bookmarks_filter_title">"Ţråçķéð þröðûçţš - one two"</string>
<string name="tracked_products_empty_list_title">"Ýöû’ļļ ƒîñð ýöûr ţråçķéð þröðûçţš ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_disabled_snackbar">"Šţöþþéð ţråçķîñĝ þrîçé - one two three"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_enabled_snackbar">"Ţråçķîñĝ þrîçé. Ĝéţ åļérţš îƒ ţĥé þrîçé ðröþš öñ åñý šîţé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_error_snackbar">"Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. Çöûļðñ’ţ ûþðåţé Ţråçķ þrîçé. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="price_tracking_error_snackbar_action">"Ţrý åĝåîñ - one two"</string>
<string name="iph_price_tracking_menu_item">"Ţråçķ þrîçé - one two"</string>
<string name="iph_price_tracking_menu_item_accessibility">"Ţråçķ þrîçé ƒröm ţĥé Möré öþţîöñš bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="iph_shopping_list_save_flow">"Örĝåñîžé ýöûr ţråçķéð þröðûçţš îñ Bööķmårķš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="iph_shopping_list_save_flow_accessibility">"Örĝåñîžé ýöûr ţråçķéð þröðûçţš îñ Bööķmårķš ƒröm ţĥé ƒöļðér îçöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="reading_list_read">"®éåð - one"</string>
<string name="reading_list_unread">"Ûñréåð - Åvåîļåbļé öƒƒļîñé - one two three"</string>
<string name="reading_list_saved">"Åððéð ţö réåðîñĝ ļîšţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="reading_list_mark_as_read">"Mårķ åš réåð - one two three"</string>
<string name="reading_list_reminder_notification_title">"Çåţçĥ ûþ öñ ýöûr réåðîñĝ ļîšţ - one two three four five six"</string>
<plurals name="reading_list_reminder_notification_subtitle">
  <item quantity="one">"Ýöû ĥåvé %1$d ûñréåð þåĝé - one two three four five"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"Ýöû ĥåvé %1$d ûñréåð þåĝéš - one two three four five"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="reading_list_unread_page_count">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$d ûñréåð þåĝé - one two three"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$d ûñréåð þåĝéš - one two three"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="reading_list_no_unread_pages">"Ñö ûñréåð þåĝéš - one two three"</string>
<string name="reading_list_save_pages_for_later">"Åðð þåĝéš ţö ýöûr réåðîñĝ ļîšţ ƒör ļåţér - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="reading_list_find_in_bookmarks">"Fîñð ýöûr réåðîñĝ ļîšţ îñ Bööķmårķš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="reading_list_empty_list_title">"Ýöû’ļļ ƒîñð ýöûr réåðîñĝ ļîšţ ĥéré - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="offline_pages_viewing_offline_page">"Vîéŵîñĝ åñ öƒƒļîñé çöþý öƒ ţĥîš þåĝé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<plurals name="offline_pages_auto_fetch_in_progress_notification_text">
  <item quantity="one">"Çĥrömé ŵîļļ ļöåð ýöûr þåĝé ŵĥéñ réåðý - one two three four five six seven"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"Çĥrömé ŵîļļ ļöåð ýöûr þåĝéš ŵĥéñ réåðý - one two three four five six seven"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="offline_pages_auto_fetch_ready_notification_text">"Þåĝé îš réåðý ţö vîéŵ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="offline_indicator_offline_title">"Ñö çöññéçţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="offline_indicator_view_offline_content">"Šéé ðöŵñļöåðš - one two"</string>
<string name="offline_indicator_v2_offline_text">"Ñö îñţérñéţ çöññéçţîöñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="offline_indicator_v2_back_online_text">"Båçķ öñļîñé - one two"</string>
<string name="hint_find_in_page">"Fîñð îñ þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="find_in_page_count">"%1$d/%2$d"</string>
<string name="accessible_find_in_page_count">"®éšûļţ %1$d öƒ %2$d - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessible_find_in_page_no_results">"Ñö réšûļţš - one two"</string>
<string name="location_bar_verbose_status_offline">"Öƒƒļîñé - one"</string>
<string name="location_bar_paint_preview_page_status">"Þrévîéŵ - one"</string>
<string name="voice_search_error">"Ñö éñåbļéð vöîçé šéårçĥ åvåîļåbļé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="open_in_new_tab_toast">"Ţåb öþéñéð îñ båçķĝröûñð. - one two three four"</string>
<string name="menu_open_in_chrome">"Öþéñ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_open_in_incognito_chrome">"Open in Incognito Chrome"</string>
<string name="menu_open_in_product">"Öþéñ îñ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="menu_open_in_product_default">"Öþéñ îñ bröŵšér - one two three"</string>
<string name="reader_view_text_alt">"Šĥöŵ šîmþļîƒîéð vîéŵ - one two three"</string>
<string name="reader_mode_message_title">"Vîéŵ šîmþļîƒîéð þåĝé¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="reader_mode_message_button">"Vîéŵ - one"</string>
<string name="content_provider_search_description">"Bööķmårķš åñð ŵéb ĥîšţörý - one two three four"</string>
<string name="chrome_survey_prompt">"Ĥéļþ îmþrövé Çĥrömé. &lt;LINK&gt;Ţåķé šûrvéý&lt;/LINK&gt; - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="chrome_survey_message_title">"Ĥéļþ îmþrövé Çĥrömé¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="chrome_survey_message_button">"Ţåķé šûrvéý - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_menu_update">"Ûþðåţé åvåîļåbļé. Möré öþţîöñš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_menu_os_version_unsupported">"Çĥrömé çåñ’ţ ûþðåţé. Möré öþţîöñš - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_mic">"Šţårţ vöîçé šéårçĥ - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_btn_lens_camera">"Šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ ýöûr çåmérå ûšîñĝ Ĝööĝļé Ļéñš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="accessibility_new_incognito_tab_page">"Ñéŵ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_new_tab">"Ñéŵ ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_new_incognito_tab">"Ñéŵ Îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_incognito_badge">"Îñçöĝñîţö möðé - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_tabswitcher_toggle_default">"Šŵîţçĥ ör çļöšé ţåbš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_identity_disc">"Måñåĝé åççöûñţ - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_home">"Ĥömé - one"</string>
<string name="accessibility_btn_refresh">"®éƒréšĥ þåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_btn_stop_loading">"Šţöþ þåĝé ļöåðîñĝ - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_find_toolbar_btn_next">"Ñéxţ - one"</string>
<string name="accessibility_find_toolbar_btn_prev">"Þrévîöûš - one"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_btn_empty_new_tab">"Ñéŵ ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_btn_incognito_toggle_standard">"Éñţér Îñçöĝñîţö möðé - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_btn_incognito_toggle_incognito">"Ļéåvé Îñçöĝñîţö möðé - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_identifier">"Ţåb - one"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_identifier_selected">"Šéļéçţéð Ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_incognito_identifier">"Îñçöĝñîţö Ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_tabstrip_incognito_identifier_selected">"Šéļéçţéð Îñçöĝñîţö Ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_refine">"®éƒîñé: %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_conceal_clipboard_contents">"Ĥîðé çļîþböårð çöñţéñţš - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_reveal_clipboard_contents">"Šĥöŵ çļîþböårð çöñţéñţš - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_conceal_button_announcement">"Çļîþböårð çöñţéñţš ĥîððéñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_reveal_button_announcement">"Çļîþböårð çöñţéñţš šĥöŵñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_switch_to_tab">"Šŵîţçĥ Ţö Ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_showing_suggestions_for_website">"Šĥöŵîñĝ šûĝĝéšţîöñš ƒör %1$s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_pedal">"Çĥrömé åçţîöñ bûţţöñ: %s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_suggested_items">"%d šûĝĝéšţéð îţémš îñ ļîšţ béļöŵ. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_most_visited_tile_search">"Šéårçĥ: %s - one two"</string>
<string name="accessibility_omnibox_most_visited_tile_navigate">"Ñåvîĝåţé: %1$s: %2$s - one two three"</string>
<plurals name="accessibility_share_selected_items">
  <item quantity="one">"Šĥåré 1 šéļéçţéð îţém - one two three four"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"Šĥåré %d šéļéçţéð îţémš - one two three four"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="accessibility_remove_selected_items">
  <item quantity="one">"®émövé 1 šéļéçţéð îţém - one two three four"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"®émövé %d šéļéçţéð îţémš - one two three four"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="accessibility_expand_section_header">"Ţåþ ţö éxþåñð - one two three"</string>
<string name="accessibility_collapse_section_header">"Ţåþ ţö çöļļåþšé - one two three"</string>
<string name="tab_switcher_button_label">"Ţåbš - one"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_network_unavailable">"Ûñåbļé ţö åççéšš ţĥé ñéţŵörķ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_error">"Érrör: %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_open">"Öþéñ îñ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_generic_map">"Öþéñ îñ måþš åþþ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_email">"Çréåţé émåîļ îñ %1$s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_generic_email">"Çréåţé émåîļ - one two"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_event">"Çréåţé évéñţ îñ %1$s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_generic_event">"Çréåţé évéñţ - one two"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_phone">"Çåļļ - one"</string>
<string name="contextual_search_quick_action_caption_generic_website">"Ĝö ţö þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="webapp_activity_title">"Ŵéb Åþþ - one two"</string>
<string name="print_share_activity_title">"Þrîñţ - one"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_share_activity_title">"Šéñð ţö ýöûr ðévîçéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="omnibox_confirm_delete">"®émövé šûĝĝéšţîöñ ƒröm ĥîšţörý¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="omnibox_confirm_delete_from_clipboard">"®émövé šûĝĝéšţîöñ ƒröm çļîþböårð¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="most_visited_tiles_header">"Fréqûéñţļý vîšîţéð - one two"</string>
<string name="undo_bar_close_message">"Çļöšéð %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="undo_bar_close_all_message">"%1$s ţåbš çļöšéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="delete_message">"Ðéļéţéð %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="undo_bar_multiple_delete_message">"%1$s bööķmårķš ðéļéţéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="undo_bar_multiple_downloads_delete_message">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåðš ðéļéţéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="undo_bar_delete_restore_accessibility_message">"®éšţöréð %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="undo_bar_multiple_downloads_delete_restore_accessibility_message">"%1$s ðöŵñļöåðš réšţöréð - one two three"</string>
<string name="unsupported_number_of_windows">"Ûñšûþþörţéð ñûmbér öƒ Çĥrömé îñšţåñçéš. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="max_number_of_windows">"Ýöû çåñ ĥåvé ûþ ţö 5 ŵîñðöŵš. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="close_tab">"Çļöšé ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="overscroll_navigation_close_chrome">"Çļöšé %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="overscroll_navigation_close_tab">"Çļöšé ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="overscroll_navigation_sheet_description">"Ñåvîĝåţîöñ ĥîšţörý - one two"</string>
<string name="overscroll_navigation_sheet_opened_half">"Ñåvîĝåţîöñ ĥîšţörý îš ĥåļƒ-öþéñéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="overscroll_navigation_sheet_opened_full">"Ñåvîĝåţîöñ ĥîšţörý îš öþéñéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="overscroll_navigation_sheet_closed">"Ñåvîĝåţîöñ ĥîšţörý îš çļöšéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="ephemeral_tab_sheet_description">"Þrévîéŵ ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="ephemeral_tab_sheet_not_viewable">"Þrévîéŵ ţåb çöñţéñţ îš ñöţ vîéŵåbļé. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="ephemeral_tab_sheet_opened_half">"Þrévîéŵ ţåb îš ĥåļƒ-öþéñéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="ephemeral_tab_sheet_opened_full">"Þrévîéŵ ţåb îš öþéñéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="ephemeral_tab_sheet_closed">"Þrévîéŵ ţåb îš çļöšéð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="feed_card_menu_description">"Fééð çårð méñû - one two three"</string>
<string name="feed_card_menu_opened_half">"Fééð çårð méñû ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="feed_card_menu_opened_full">"Fééð çårð méñû îš öþéñéð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="feed_card_menu_closed">"Fééð çårð méñû îš çļöšéð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="feed_autoplay_title">"Åûţöþļåý - one"</string>
<string name="video_previews_title">"Vîðéö þrévîéŵš - one two"</string>
<string name="video_previews_summary">"Çĥööšé ĥöŵ vîðéö þrévîéŵš ŵîļļ åûţömåţîçåļļý þļåý öñ ţĥé Çĥrömé ĥöméþåĝé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="video_previews_option_never">"Ñévér - one"</string>
<string name="video_previews_option_wifi">"Öñļý öñ Ŵî-Fî - one two three"</string>
<string name="video_previews_option_wifi_and_mobile_data">"Öñ Ŵî-Fî &amp; möbîļé ðåţå - one two three four"</string>
<string name="web_feed_follow_loading_description">"Föļļöŵîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="web_feed_follow_success_snackbar_message">"Föļļöŵîñĝ %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="web_feed_follow_success_snackbar_action">"Ĝö ţö ƒééð - one two three"</string>
<string name="web_feed_follow_generic_failure_snackbar_message">"Çåñ’ţ ƒöļļöŵ. Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="web_feed_unfollow_generic_failure_snackbar_message">"Çåñ’ţ ûñƒöļļöŵ. Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="web_feed_offline_failure_snackbar_message">"Ýöû\'ré öƒƒļîñé. Çĥéçķ ýöûr îñţérñéţ çöññéçţîöñ åñð ţrý åĝåîñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="web_feed_generic_failure_snackbar_action">"Ţrý åĝåîñ - one two"</string>
<string name="web_feed_unfollow_success_snackbar_message">"Ûñƒöļļöŵéð %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="web_feed_unfollow_success_snackbar_action">"®éƒöļļöŵ - one"</string>
<string name="web_feed_post_follow_dialog_title">"Ýöû’ré ƒöļļöŵîñĝ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="web_feed_post_follow_dialog_stories_ready_description">"Ýöû\'ļļ ñöŵ šéé šţörîéš ƒröm %1$s ŵĥéñ ýöû öþéñ å ñéŵ ţåb. Šîţéš ýöû ƒöļļöŵ åré šåvéð îñ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ. Ýöû çåñ måñåĝé ţĥém îñ Ðîšçövér šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="web_feed_post_follow_dialog_stories_not_ready_description">"Šööñ, ýöû’ļļ šéé šţörîéš ƒröm %1$s ŵĥéñ ýöû öþéñ å ñéŵ ţåb. Šîţéš ýöû ƒöļļöŵ åré šåvéð îñ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ. Ýöû çåñ måñåĝé ţĥém îñ Ðîšçövér šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="web_feed_post_follow_dialog_open_a_new_tab">"Öþéñ å ñéŵ ţåb - one two three four"</string>
<string name="storage_management_activity_label">"Ĝööĝļé %1$s šţöråĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="storage_management_unimportant_site_data_description">"Šţöréð ðåţå ţĥåţ Çĥrömé ðöéšñ\'ţ ţĥîñķ îš îmþörţåñţ (é.ĝ. šîţéš ŵîţĥ ñö šåvéð šéţţîñĝš ör ţĥåţ ýöû ðöñ\'ţ vîšîţ öƒţéñ) - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="storage_management_unimportant_site_data_size_label">"Ûñîmþörţåñţ ðåţå - one two"</string>
<string name="storage_management_clear_unimportant_site_data_button">"Fréé ûþ šþåçé - one two three"</string>
<string name="storage_management_clear_unimportant_dialog_text">"Ţĥîš ŵîļļ çļéår çööķîéš, çåçĥé, åñð öţĥér ðåţå öƒ šîţéš Çĥrömé ðöéšñ\'ţ ţĥîñķ îš îmþörţåñţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="storage_management_site_data_description">"Åļļ ðåţå šţöréð bý šîţéš, îñçļûðîñĝ çööķîéš åñð öţĥér ļöçåļļý šţöréð ðåţå - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="storage_management_computing_size">"Çömþûţîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="storage_management_startup_failure">"Ûñķñöŵñ - one"</string>
<string name="storage_management_site_data_size_label">"Šîţé šţöråĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="storage_management_manage_site_data_button">"Måñåĝé - one"</string>
<string name="storage_management_all_storage_description">"Ţöţåļ ðåţå ûšéð bý Çĥrömé, îñçļûðîñĝ åççöûñţš, bööķmårķš, åñð šåvéð šéţţîñĝš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="storage_management_clear_all_data_button">"Çļéår Åļļ Ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="storage_management_reset_app_dialog_title">"Ðéļéţé åþþ ðåţå¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="storage_management_reset_app_dialog_text">"Åļļ Çĥrömé’š åþþ ðåţå ŵîļļ bé ðéļéţéð þérmåñéñţļý. Ţĥîš îñçļûðéš åļļ ƒîļéš, šéţţîñĝš, åççöûñţš, ðåţåbåšéš, éţç. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="usb_chooser_dialog_prompt">"%1$s ŵåñţš ţö çöññéçţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="usb_chooser_dialog_no_devices_found_prompt">"Ñö çömþåţîbļé ðévîçéš ƒöûñð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="usb_chooser_dialog_connect_button_text">"Çöññéçţ - one"</string>
<string name="usb_chooser_dialog_footnote_text">"&lt;link&gt;Ĝéţ ĥéļþ&lt;/link&gt; - one two three four"</string>
<string name="search_with_sogou">"Šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ Šöĝöû - one two three"</string>
<string name="sogou_explanation">"Çĥrömé çåñ ûšé &lt;b&gt;Šöĝöû&lt;/b&gt; ƒör šéårçĥ îñ Çĥîñå. Ýöû çåñ çĥåñĝé ţĥîš îñ &lt;link&gt;Šéţţîñĝš&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="keep_google">"Ķééþ Ĝööĝļé - one two"</string>
<string name="using_sogou">"Ûšîñĝ Šöĝöû ƒör šéårçĥ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="using_google">"Ûšîñĝ Ĝööĝļé ƒör šéårçĥ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="twa_running_in_chrome">"®ûññîñĝ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three"</string>
<string name="twa_running_in_chrome_template">"®ûññîñĝ îñ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="twa_running_in_chrome_v2">"Ýöû\'ļļ šéé ýöûr %1$s šîĝñ-îñ šţåţûš, bröŵšîñĝ ðåţå, åñð šîţé ðåţå îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="twa_clear_data_dialog_title">"%1$s åļšö ĥåš ðåţå îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="twa_clear_data_dialog_message">"Ýöû çåñ çļéår ţĥé ðåţå îñ Çĥrömé Šéţţîñĝš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="twa_clear_data_dialog_keep_data">"Ķééþ Ðåţå - one two"</string>
<string name="twa_clear_data_site_selection_title">"Ļîñķéð šîţéš - one two"</string>
<string name="twa_quality_enforcement_violation_error">"%1$s öñ %2$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="twa_quality_enforcement_violation_asset_link">"Ðîĝîţåļ åššéţ ļîñķš vérîƒîçåţîöñ ƒåîļéð öñ %1$s - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="twa_quality_enforcement_violation_offline">"Þåĝé ûñåvåîļåbļé öƒƒļîñé: %1$s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="webapp_tap_to_copy_url">"Ţåþ ţö çöþý ţĥé Û®Ļ ƒör ţĥîš åþþ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="webapk_offline_dialog">"Ţö ûšé %1$s ƒör ţĥé ƒîršţ ţîmé, þļéåšé çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé îñţérñéţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="webapk_notification_channel_name">"Ĝéñéråļ - one"</string>
<string name="webapk_cannot_connect_to_site">"Çåñ\'ţ çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé šîţé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="webapk_network_error_message_tunnel_connection_failed">"Éšţåbļîšĥîñĝ å ţûññéļ vîå þröxý šérvér ƒåîļéð - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="launchpad_title">"Åþþš - one"</string>
<string name="launchpad_menu_uninstall">"Ûñîñšţåļļ - one"</string>
<string name="launchpad_menu_site_settings">"Šîţé šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_open_new_tab">"Öþéñ å ñéŵ ţåb - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_reopen_new_tab">"®éöþéñ ţĥé ļåšţ çļöšéð ţåb - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_new_incognito_tab">"Öþéñ å ñéŵ ţåb îñ Îñçöĝñîţö möðé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_open_menu">"Öþéñ ţĥé méñû - one two three"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_next_tab">"Ĵûmþ ţö ţĥé ñéxţ ţåb - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_prev_tab">"Ĵûmþ ţö ţĥé þrévîöûš ţåb - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_close_tab">"Çļöšé çûrréñţ ţåb - one two three"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_find_bar">"Öþéñ ţĥé Fîñð Bår - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_address_bar">"Ĵûmþ ţö ţĥé åððréšš bår - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_bookmark_manager">"Öþéñ ţĥé bööķmårķš måñåĝér - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_bookmark_page">"Bööķmårķ ţĥé çûrréñţ þåĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_history_manager">"Öþéñ ţĥé ĥîšţörý þåĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_print_page">"Öþéñ öþţîöñš ţö þrîñţ þåĝé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_zoom_in">"Måķé évérýţĥîñĝ öñ ţĥé þåĝé bîĝĝér - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_zoom_out">"Måķé évérýţĥîñĝ öñ ţĥé þåĝé šmåļļér - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_reset_zoom">"®éţûrñ évérýţĥîñĝ öñ ţĥé þåĝé ţö ðéƒåûļţ šîžé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_reload_page">"®éļöåð ţĥé çûrréñţ þåĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_reload_no_cache">"®éļöåð ţĥé çûrréñţ þåĝé, îĝñörîñĝ çåçĥéð çöñţéñţ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_help_center">"Öþéñ ţĥé Çĥrömé Ĥéļþ Çéñţér îñ å ñéŵ ţåb - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_tab_group_header">"Ţåb åñð ŵîñðöŵ šĥörţçûţš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_chrome_feature_group_header">"Ĝööĝļé Çĥrömé ƒéåţûré šĥörţçûţš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="keyboard_shortcut_webpage_group_header">"Ŵébþåĝé šĥörţçûţš - one two"</string>
<string name="vr_module_title">"Vîrţûåļ ®éåļîţý - one two"</string>
<string name="vr_preparing_vr_toast_standalone_text">"Çĥrömé îš šţîļļ þréþårîñĝ ƒör V®. ®éšţårţ Çĥrömé ļåţér. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="vr_preparing_vr_notification_title">"Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. - one two three"</string>
<string name="vr_preparing_vr_notification_body">"®éöþéñ Çĥrömé. - one two"</string>
<string name="ar_module_title">"Åûĝméñţéð ®éåļîţý - one two"</string>
<string name="module_install_start_text">"Îñšţåļļîñĝ %1$s ƒör Çĥrömé… - one two three four"</string>
<string name="module_install_success_text">"Îñšţåļļéð - one"</string>
<string name="module_install_failure_text">"Ûñåbļé ţö îñšţåļļ %1$s ƒör Çĥrömé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="instant_apps_message_title">"Öþéñ åþþ ƒör %1$s¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_instant_apps_message_title_content_description">"Öþéñ åþþ ƒör %1$s ŵîţĥ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_image_title">"ÎMÅĜÉ - one"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_link_title">"ĻÎÑĶ - one"</string>
<string name="contextmenu_video_title">"VÎÐÉÖ - one"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_header">"Måñåĝé ŵîñðöŵš - one two"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_entry_empty_window">"Émþţý ŵîñðöŵ - one two"</string>
<plurals name="instance_switcher_desc_incognito">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s îñçöĝñîţö ţåb - one two three"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš - one two three"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="instance_switcher_desc_mixed">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s ţåb - one two three four"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%2$s ţåbš, %1$s îñçöĝñîţö - one two three four"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="instance_switcher_tab_count_zero">"Ñö ţåbš - one two"</string>
<plurals name="instance_switcher_tab_count_nonzero">
  <item quantity="one">"1 ţåb - one two"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%d ţåbš - one two"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="instance_switcher_close_window">"Çļöšé ŵîñðöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_current_window">"Çûrréñţ - one"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_adjacent_window">"Ŵîñðöŵ îš öþéñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_already_running_foreground">"Çĥrömé îš åļréåðý rûññîñĝ ĥéré. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="target_selector_move">"Mövé ţåb - one two"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_close_confirm_header">"Çļöšé ŵîñðöŵ¿ - one two"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_close_confirm_deleted_tabs_zero">"Ţĥé ŵîñðöŵ ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="instance_switcher_close_confirm_deleted_tabs_one">"Ţĥé ţåb %1$s ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five six"</string>
<plurals name="instance_switcher_close_confirm_deleted_tabs_many">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s åñð %2$s möré ţåb ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five six seven eight"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s åñð %2$s möré ţåbš ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five six seven eight"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="instance_switcher_close_confirm_deleted_incognito">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s îñçöĝñîţö ţåb ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five six"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five six"</item>
</plurals>
<plurals name="instance_switcher_close_confirm_deleted_incognito_mixed">
  <item quantity="one">"%1$s îñçöĝñîţö åñð %2$s möré ţåb ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</item>
  <item quantity="other">"%1$s îñçöĝñîţö åñð %2$s möré ţåbš ŵîļļ bé çļöšéð - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</item>
</plurals>
<string name="iph_download_page_for_offline_usage_text">"Ðöŵñļöåð þåĝéš ţö ûšé ţĥém öƒƒļîñé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="iph_download_page_for_offline_usage_accessibility_text">"Ðöŵñļöåð þåĝéš ƒröm ţĥé Möré öþţîöñš bûţţöñ ţö ûšé ţĥém öƒƒļîñé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="iph_download_home_text">"Fîñð ýöûr ƒîļéš åñð þåĝéš îñ Ðöŵñļöåðš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="iph_download_home_accessibility_text">"Fîñð ýöûr ƒîļéš åñð þåĝéš îñ Ðöŵñļöåðš ƒröm ţĥé Möré Öþţîöñš bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="iph_download_indicator_text">"Šéé ýöûr öƒƒļîñé ƒîļéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="iph_identity_disc_text">"Måñåĝé ýöûr åççöûñţ - one two three"</string>
<string name="iph_instance_switcher_text">"Ĝöţ måñý ŵîñðöŵš¿ Ýöû çåñ måñåĝé ţĥém ƒröm ĥéré - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="iph_identity_disc_accessibility_text">"Ţö måñåĝé ýöûr Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ, ţåþ ţĥé \"Måñåĝé åççöûñţ\" bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="iph_mic_toolbar_generic_message_text">"Šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ ýöûr vöîçé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="iph_mic_toolbar_generic_message_accessibility_text">"Ţåþ ţĥé mîç ţö šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ ýöûr vöîçé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="iph_mic_toolbar_example_query_text">"Ţrý “Ŵĥåţ’š ţĥé ŵéåţĥér ţöðåý¿” - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="iph_mic_toolbar_example_query_accessibility_text">"Ţö çĥéçķ ţĥé ŵéåţĥér, ţåþ ţĥé mîç åñð šåý “Ŵĥåţ’š ţĥé ŵéåţĥér ţöðåý¿” - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="iph_ntp_without_feed_text">"Šéé ýöûr ţöþ šîţéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="iph_ntp_without_feed_accessibility_text">"Ţö šéé ýöûr ţöþ šîţéš, ţåþ ţĥé Ĥömé bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="iph_ntp_with_feed_text">"Šéé ţöþ šîţéš åñð šţörîéš ƒör ýöû - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="iph_ntp_with_feed_accessibility_text">"Ţö šéé ţöþ šîţéš åñð šţörîéš ƒör ýöû, ţåþ ţĥé Ĥömé bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="iph_tab_switcher_text">"Öþéñ ţåbš ţö vîšîţ ðîƒƒéréñţ þåĝéš åţ ţĥé šåmé ţîmé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="iph_tab_switcher_accessibility_text">"Ţö öþéñ ţåbš åñð vîšîţ ðîƒƒéréñţ þåĝéš åţ ţĥé šåmé ţîmé, ţåþ ţĥé öþéñ ţåbš bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="iph_translate_menu_button_text">"Ţråñšļåţé ţĥîš þåĝé ţö åñý ļåñĝûåĝé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="iph_translate_menu_button_accessibility_text">"Ţråñšļåţé ţĥîš þåĝé ţö åñý ļåñĝûåĝé ƒröm ţĥé Möré öþţîöñš bûţţöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="iph_shared_highlighting_builder">"Ñéŵ: šĥåré å ļîñķ ţĥåţ šçröļļš ţö ţĥîš ţéxţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="search_widget_default">"Šéårçĥ - one"</string>
<string name="search_with_product">"Šéårçĥ ŵîţĥ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="iph_download_settings_text">"Çĥåñĝé ţĥé ðéƒåûļţ ðöŵñļöåð ļöçåţîöñ åñý ţîmé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="iph_download_settings_accessibility_text">"Çĥåñĝé ţĥé ðéƒåûļţ ðöŵñļöåð ļöçåţîöñ åñý ţîmé ûšîñĝ ţĥé Šéţţîñĝš méñû öþţîöñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="iph_download_infobar_download_continuing_text">"Ýöûr ðöŵñļöåð îš šţîļļ îñ þröĝréšš - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="quick_action_search_widget_search_bar_hint">"Šéårçĥ ör ţýþé Û®Ļ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="accessibility_quick_action_search_widget_start_dino_game">"Šţårţ Ðîñö Ĝåmé - one two three"</string>
<string name="quick_action_search_widget_message_no_incognito">"Îñçöĝñîţö îš ñöţ åvåîļåbļé öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="quick_action_search_widget_message_no_voice_search">"Vöîçé šéårçĥ îš ñöţ åvåîļåbļé öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="quick_action_search_widget_message_no_google_lens">"Ĝööĝļé Ļéñš îš ñöţ åvåîļåbļé öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="dino_widget_text">"Çĥrömé Ðîñö - one two"</string>
<string name="disabled_incognito_launcher_shortcut_message">"®émövé åñð réçréåţé ţĥîš šĥörţçûţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_toast">"Šéñðîñĝ ţö %1$s… - one two three"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_notification_context_text">"%1$s - Šéñţ ƒröm %2$s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_content_description">"Ļîšţ öƒ ðévîçéš ţö šĥåré å ţåb ŵîţĥ. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_sheet_half_height">"Ļîšţ öƒ ðévîçéš ţö šĥåré å ţåb ŵîţĥ öþéñéð åţ ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_sheet_full_height">"Ļîšţ öƒ ðévîçéš ţö šĥåré å ţåb ŵîţĥ öþéñéð åţ ƒûļļ ĥéîĝĥţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_sheet_closed">"Ļîšţ öƒ ðévîçéš ţö šĥåré å ţåb ŵîţĥ îš çļöšéð. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_sheet_toolbar">"Šéñð ţö - one two"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_device_last_active_more_than_one_day">"Åçţîvé %1$d ðåýš åĝö - one two three four"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_device_last_active_one_day_ago">"Åçţîvé 1 ðåý åĝö - one two three four"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_device_last_active_today">"Åçţîvé ţöðåý - one two"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_device_type_generic">"ðévîçé - one"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_device_type_phone">"þĥöñé - one"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_device_type_computer">"çömþûţér - one"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_v2_toast">"Þåĝé šéñţ. Ţö šéé îţ, öþéñ Çĥrömé öñ ýöûr %1$s - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_manage_devices_link">"&lt;link&gt;Ýöûr ðévîçéš&lt;/link&gt; · %1$s - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_when_signed_in_unavailable">"Ýöû çåñ šéñð ţåbš béţŵééñ ðévîçéš ţĥåţ åré šîĝñéð îñ ŵîţĥ ţĥé šåmé Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="send_tab_to_self_android_no_target_device_label">"Ţö šéñð ţĥîš ţåb ţö åñöţĥér ðévîçé, šîĝñ îñ ţö Çĥrömé ţĥéré - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_sending_notification_title">"Šĥårîñĝ ţö %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_no_devices_available_text">"Ţö šĥåré ţĥîš þåĝé ţö åñöţĥér ðévîçé, ţûrñ öñ šýñç îñ Çĥrömé šéţţîñĝš öñ ţĥé öţĥér ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_storage_disabled_text">"Ýöû ĥåvé ðîšåbļéð Šţöråĝé åççéšš, þļéåšé ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš ţö éñåbļé îţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_open_settings_label">"Öþéñ Šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_audio_preview_subtitle">"åûðîö - one"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_image_preview_subtitle">"îmåĝé - one"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_text_preview_subtitle">"ţéxţ - one"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_video_preview_subtitle">"vîðéö - one"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_content_description">"Ļîšţ öƒ šĥårîñĝ öþţîöñš. - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_sheet_half_height">"Ļîšţ öƒ šĥårîñĝ öþţîöñš öþéñéð åţ ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_sheet_full_height">"Ļîšţ öƒ šĥårîñĝ öþţîöñš åţ ƒûļļ ĥéîĝĥţ. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sharing_hub_sheet_closed">"Ļîšţ öƒ šĥårîñĝ öþţîöñš îš çļöšéð. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="click_to_call_notification_text">"Ţåþ ţö måķé çåļļ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="click_to_call_dialer_absent_notification_title">"Çåñ\'ţ måķé çåļļš - one two three"</string>
<string name="click_to_call_dialer_absent_notification_text">"Måķé šûré å þĥöñé åþþ îš éñåbļéð öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_content_type_text">"ţéxţ - one"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_error_dialog_title_generic_error">"Çåñ\'ţ šĥåré %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_error_dialog_title_internal_error">"Çöûļðñ\'ţ šĥåré %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_error_dialog_text_device_not_found">"Måķé šûré %1$s ĥåš šýñç ţûrñéð öñ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_error_dialog_text_network_error">"Måķé šûré ţĥîš ðévîçé îš çöññéçţéð ţö ţĥé îñţérñéţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_error_dialog_text_device_ack_timeout">"Måķé šûré %1$s îš çöññéçţéð ţö ţĥé îñţérñéţ - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_error_dialog_text_internal_error">"Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. Ţrý åĝåîñ ļåţér. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_shared_clipboard_error_dialog_title_payload_too_large">"Ţéxţ îš ţöö ļårĝé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="browser_sharing_shared_clipboard_error_dialog_text_payload_too_large">"Ţrý šĥårîñĝ ţĥé ţéxţ îñ šmåļļér çĥûñķš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="shared_clipboard_notification_title_unknown_device">"Ţéxţ šĥåréð ƒröm öţĥér ðévîçé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="shared_clipboard_notification_title">"Ţéxţ šĥåréð ƒröm %1$s - one two three four"</string>
<string name="shared_clipboard_notification_text">"Çöþîéð ţö ýöûr çļîþböårð - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sms_fetcher_notification_title">"Šûbmîţ %1$s öñ %2$s¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sms_fetcher_notification_text">"Ļéţ %1$s vérîƒý îţ\'š ýöû - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sms_fetcher_notification_text_for_embedded_frame">"Ļéţ %1$s vérîƒý îţ\'š ýöû ƒör %2$s - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="sms_fetcher_notification_title_simple_string">"Šûbmîţ %1$s ţö %2$s¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="redirect_blocked_message">"®éðîréçţ bļöçķéð: - one two"</string>
<string name="redirect_blocked_short_message">"®éðîréçţ bļöçķéð. - one two"</string>
<string name="always_allow_redirects">"Åļŵåýš åļļöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="near_oom_intervention_message">"Ţĥîš þåĝé ûšéš ţöö mûçĥ mémörý, šö Çĥrömé þåûšéð îţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="near_oom_intervention_decline">"®éšûmé - one"</string>
<string name="near_oom_reduction_message">"Ţĥîš þåĝé ûšéš ţöö mûçĥ mémörý, šö Çĥrömé rémövéð šömé çöñţéñţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="near_oom_reduction_decline">"Šĥöŵ örîĝîñåļ - one two"</string>
<string name="prefs_autofill_assistant_title">"Ĝööĝļé Åššîšţåñţ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="prefs_autofill_assistant_summary">"Ĥéļþš ýöû çömþļéţé ţåšķš, šûçĥ åš çĥéçķöûţ, ţĥröûĝĥöûţ ţĥé ŵéb - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="prefs_web_assistance_section_title">"Ŵéb Åššîšţåñçé - one two"</string>
<string name="prefs_autofill_assistant_get_help_title">"Ĝéţ ĥéļþ ŵîţĥ ţåšķš öñ ţĥé ŵéb - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="prefs_autofill_assistant_get_help_summary">"Ţö ĥéļþ ýöû çömþļéţé ţåšķš, Ĝööĝļé ŵîļļ réçéîvé ţĥé Û®Ļš åñð çöñţéñţš öƒ šîţéš öñ ŵĥîçĥ ýöû ûšé Åššîšţåñţ, åš ŵéļļ åš îñƒörmåţîöñ ýöû šûbmîţ ţĥröûĝĥ Åššîšţåñţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="prefs_autofill_assistant_proactive_help_title">"Þröåçţîvé Ĥéļþ - one two"</string>
<string name="prefs_autofill_assistant_proactive_help_summary">"Åššîšţåñţ ŵîļļ åþþéår ŵĥéñ îţ ðéţéçţš ţĥåţ îţ çåñ ĥéļþ ýöû öñ šûþþörţéð ŵébšîţéš - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="prefs_proactive_help_sync_link">"Ţö ûšé ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ &lt;link&gt;Måķé šéårçĥéš åñð bröŵšîñĝ béţţér&lt;/link&gt; mûšţ bé ţûrñéð öñ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="usage_stats_consent_title">"Šĥöŵ ýöûr Çĥrömé åçţîvîţý îñ Ðîĝîţåļ Ŵéļļbéîñĝ¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="usage_stats_consent_prompt">"Ýöû çåñ šéé šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ îñ Çĥrömé åñð šéţ ţîmérš ƒör ţĥém.\ñ\ñĜööĝļé ĝéţš îñƒö åböûţ ţĥé šîţéš ýöû šéţ ţîmérš ƒör åñð ĥöŵ ļöñĝ ýöû vîšîţ ţĥém. Ţĥîš îñƒö îš ûšéð ţö måķé Ðîĝîţåļ Ŵéļļbéîñĝ béţţér. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="usage_stats_setting_title">"®émövé ýöûr Çĥrömé åçţîvîţý ƒröm Ðîĝîţåļ Ŵéļļbéîñĝ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="usage_stats_revocation_prompt">"®émövé ýöûr Çĥrömé åçţîvîţý ƒröm Ðîĝîţåļ Ŵéļļbéîñĝ¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="usage_stats_revocation_explanation">"Šîţéš ýöû vîšîţ îñ Çĥrömé ŵöñ\'ţ šĥöŵ. Åļļ šîţé ţîmérš ŵîļļ bé ðéļéţéð. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="usage_stats_site_paused">"Šîţé þåûšéð - one two"</string>
<string name="usage_stats_site_paused_explanation">"Ýöûr %1$s ţîmér råñ öûţ. Îţ\'ļļ šţårţ åĝåîñ ţömörröŵ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="tab_management_module_title">"Ţåb måñåĝéméñţ - one two"</string>
<string name="autofill_assistant_module_title">"Ĝööĝļé Åššîšţåñţ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="dev_ui_module_title">"Ðévéļöþér ÛÎ - one two"</string>
<string name="test_dummy_module_title">"Test Dummy"</string>
<string name="stack_unwinder_module_title">"Šţåçķ Ûñŵîñðér - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_authenticator_module_title">"Þĥöñé åš å Šéçûrîţý Ķéý Šûþþörţ - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="cablev2_activity_title">"Ĝööĝļé Çĥrömé åš å Šéçûrîţý Ķéý - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="cablev2_registration_succeeded">"®éĝîšţråţîöñ šûççééðéð - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_registration_failed">"®éĝîšţråţîöñ ƒåîļéð - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_sign_in_succeeded">"Šîĝñ-îñ šûççééðéð - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_sign_in_failed">"Šîĝñ-îñ ƒåîļéð - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_usb_discon_title">"Çöññéçţéð ŵîţĥ ÛŠB çåbļé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="cablev2_usb_discon_body">"Ðîšçöññéçţ ŵĥéñ ýöû’ré ðöñé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="cablev2_serverlink_connecting_to_your_device">"Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö ýöûr ðévîçé… - one two three four"</string>
<string name="cablev2_serverlink_status_connecting">"Ţĥîš måý ţåķé å mîñûţé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="cablev2_fcm_status_connecting">"Þļåçé ýöûr þĥöñé çļöšé ţö ţĥé çömþûţér - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="cablev2_serverlink_status_connected">"Çöññéçţéð ţö ðévîçé - one two three"</string>
<string name="cablev2_serverlink_status_processing">"Þröçéššîñĝ réqûéšţ - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_serverlink_status_dfm_install">"Ûþðåţîñĝ Çĥrömé ţö çöññéçţ ţö öţĥér ðévîçéš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_title">"Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ - one two three"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_timeout">"Çåñ’ţ çöññéçţ ţö ýöûr çömþûţér. Ţrý åñöţĥér vérîƒîçåţîöñ öþţîöñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_ble_permission">"%1$s ñééðš Ñéårbý ðévîçéš þérmîššîöñ îñ örðér ţö çöññéçţ ţö ýöûr ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_no_screenlock">"Ţö ûšé ţĥîš ðévîçé åš å šéçûrîţý ķéý, šéţ å šçrééñ ļöçķ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_disco_cred">"Ţĥîš vérîƒîçåţîöñ méţĥöð îšñ’ţ åvåîļåbļé ƒör ţĥîš ðévîçé. Þîçķ å ðîƒƒéréñţ öþţîöñ öñ ýöûr öţĥér ðévîçé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_generic">"Ţrý åñöţĥér vérîƒîçåţîöñ öþţîöñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_code">"(Érrör %1$d) - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_error_close">"Çļöšé - one"</string>
<string name="cablev2_make_credential_notification_body">"Ýöûr çömþûţér ŵåñţš ţö réĝîšţér ţĥîš ðévîçé ƒör šîĝñîñĝ îñ ţö å šîţé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="cablev2_get_assertion_notification_body">"Ýöûr çömþûţér ŵåñţš ţö ûšé ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö šîĝñ îñ ţö å šîţé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="cablev2_ble_enable_title">"Ţûrñîñĝ öñ Bļûéţööţĥ… - one two three"</string>
<string name="cablev2_paask_title">"Þĥöñé åš å šéçûrîţý ķéý - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="cablev2_paask_body">"Çöñţröļ ŵĥîçĥ ðévîçéš çåñ šîĝñ îñ bý ûšîñĝ ţĥîš ðévîçé åš å šéçûrîţý ķéý. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="cablev2_your_devices">"Ýöûr ðévîçéš - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_your_devices_body">"Ŵĥéñ ýöû’ré šîĝñéð îñţö ţĥé šåmé Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ, öţĥér ðévîçéš çåñ ûšé ţĥîš þĥöñé åš å šéçûrîţý ķéý. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="cablev2_linked_devices">"Ļîñķéð ðévîçéš - one two"</string>
<string name="cablev2_linked_devices_body">"Ŵĥéñ ýöû ļîñķ åñöţĥér ðévîçé ŵîţĥ å Q® çöðé, îţ çåñ ûšé ţĥîš þĥöñé åš å šéçûrîţý ķéý. Îƒ ýöû rémövé îţ, ýöû’ļļ ĥåvé ţö šçåñ å Q® çöðé ţö ļîñķ îţ åĝåîñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="cablev2_unlink_button">"®émövé åļļ ļîñķéð ðévîçéš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="cablev2_unlink_confirmation">"®émövéð - one"</string>
<string name="cablev2_qr_title">"Çöññéçţ ŵîţĥ Q® Çöðé¿ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="cablev2_qr_body_phone">"Ýöû çåñ ûšé ţĥîš þĥöñé ţö šîĝñ îñ öñ ţĥé çömþûţér ţĥåţ’š ðîšþļåýîñĝ ţĥîš Q® çöðé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="cablev2_qr_body_tablet">"Ýöû çåñ ûšé ţĥîš ţåbļéţ ţö šîĝñ îñ öñ ţĥé çömþûţér ţĥåţ’š ðîšþļåýîñĝ ţĥîš Q® çöðé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="cablev2_qr_remember">"®émémbér ţĥîš çömþûţér - one two three"</string>
<string name="cablev2_qr_allow">"Åļļöŵ - one"</string>
<string name="cablev2_qr_dont_allow">"Ðöñ’ţ åļļöŵ - one two"</string>
<string name="qr_code_share_icon_label">"Q® Çöðé - one two"</string>
<string name="qr_code_share_tab_label">"Šĥåré - one"</string>
<string name="qr_code_scan_tab_label">"Šçåñ - one"</string>
<string name="qr_code_share_description">"Ţö šĥåré ŵîţĥ þéöþļé ñéårbý, ļéţ ţĥém šçåñ ţĥîš Q® Çöðé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="qr_code_download">"Ðöŵñļöåð - one"</string>
<string name="qr_code_error_too_long">"Çåñ\'ţ çréåţé Q® Çöðé. Û®Ļ îš möré ţĥåñ %1$d çĥåråçţérš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="qr_code_error_unknown">"Çåñ\'ţ çréåţé Q® Çöðé - one two three four"</string>
<string name="sharing_more_icon_label">"Möré - one"</string>
<string name="sharing_copy">"Çöþý - one"</string>
<string name="sharing_copy_url">"Çöþý ļîñķ - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_copy_text">"Çöþý ţéxţ - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_copy_image">"Çöþý îmåĝé - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_copy_gif">"Çöþý ĜÎF - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_lightweight_reactions">"Åðð émöţîöñ - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_screenshot">"Šçrééñšĥöţ - one"</string>
<string name="sharing_long_screenshot">"Ļöñĝ Šçrééñšĥöţ - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_long_screenshot_instructions">"Ðråĝ ţö ţåķé å ļöñĝ šçrééñšĥöţ - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="sharing_long_screenshot_move_up_button_description">"Mövé Ûþ - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_long_screenshot_move_down_button_description">"Mövé Ðöŵñ - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_long_screenshot_reached_top">"Çåñ\û2019ţ ĝö ĥîĝĥér. Ţrý šţårţîñĝ ƒröm ƒûrţĥér ûþ ţĥé þåĝé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="sharing_long_screenshot_reached_bottom">"Çåñ\û2019ţ ĝö ļöŵér. Ţrý šţårţîñĝ ƒröm ƒûrţĥér ðöŵñ ţĥé þåĝé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="sharing_long_screenshot_unknown_error">"Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. Ţrý åĝåîñ. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sharing_webnotes_create_card">"Çréåţé çårð - one two"</string>
<string name="sharing_webnotes_accessibility_description">"Çréåţé šţýļîžéð çårð ŵîţĥ ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="sharing_save_image">"Šåvé ţö ðévîçé - one two three"</string>
<string name="sharing_copied">"Çöþîéð - one"</string>
<string name="text_copied">"Ţéxţ Çöþîéð - one two"</string>
<string name="image_copied">"Îmåĝé Çöþîéð - one two"</string>
<string name="gif_copied">"ĜÎF Çöþîéð - one two"</string>
<string name="qr_code_camera_framing_rect_description">"Þöšîţîöñ Q® Çöðé/bårçöðé îñ ţĥîš ƒråmé. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="qr_code_permission_description">"Ţö šçåñ å Q® Çöðé, ļéţ Çĥrömé ûšé ýöûr çåmérå - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="qr_code_open_settings_description">"Ţö šçåñ å Q® Çöðé, çĥåñĝé ýöûr šéţţîñĝš šö ţĥåţ Çĥrömé çåñ ûšé ýöûr çåmérå - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="qr_code_permission_continue_label">"Çöñţîñûé - one"</string>
<string name="qr_code_no_camera_error">"Ţö šçåñ å Q® Çöðé, ûšé å ðévîçé ŵîţĥ å çåmérå. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="qr_code_disabled_camera_error">"Ţĥé örĝåñîžåţîöñ ţĥåţ måñåĝéš ýöûr ðévîçé ĥåš ţûrñéð öƒƒ ýöûr çåmérå. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="qr_code_in_use_camera_error">"Çåñ\'ţ öþéñ ýöûr çåmérå. ®éšţårţ ýöûr ðévîçé åñð ţrý åĝåîñ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="qr_code_hardware_camera_error">"Çåñ\'ţ öþéñ ýöûr çåmérå. Šöméţĥîñĝ ŵéñţ ŵröñĝ. - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="qr_code_open_settings_label">"Öþéñ Šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="qr_code_not_a_url_label">"Ţĥîš Q® Çöðé îš ñöţ å Û®Ļ: %1$s - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="qr_code_filename_prefix">"çĥrömé_qrçöðé_%1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="link_to_text_failure_toast_message_v2">"Çåñ’ţ çréåţé ļîñķ ţö ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="link_to_text_success_link_toast_message">"Îñçļûðé ļîñķ ţö ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="link_to_text_success_text_toast_message">"Šĥåré ţéxţ öñļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="new_badge">"Ñéŵ - one"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_iph">"Îñçļûðé å ļîñķ ţö ţĥé þåĝé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_include_link">"Îñçļûðé ļîñķ - one two"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_share_webnote_only">"Šĥåré çårð öñļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_share_screenshot_only">"Šĥåré šçrééñšĥöţ öñļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_share_image_only">"Šĥåré îmåĝé öñļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_share_gif_only">"Šĥåré ĜÎF öñļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_share_reaction_only">"Šĥåré réåçţîöñ öñļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="link_toggle_share_content_only">"Šĥåré çöñţéñţ öñļý - one two three"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_creating_gif">"Çréåţîñĝ ĜÎF %1$d%% - one two three"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_creating_gif_announcement">"Çréåţîñĝ ĜÎF - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_reaction_moved_announcement">"®éåçţîöñ mövéð - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_reaction_deleted_announcement">"®éåçţîöñ ðéļéţéð - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_reaction_duplicated_announcement">"®éåçţîöñ ðûþļîçåţéð - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_toolbar_announcement">"Çĥööšé åñ émöţîöñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_reaction_changed_announcement">"®éåçţîöñ çĥåñĝéð - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_reaction_added_announcement">"®éåçţîöñ åððéð - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_resize_and_rotate_button">"®éšîžé åñð röţåţé - one two three"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_reaction_adjusted_announcement">"®éåçţîöñ åðĵûšţéð - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_duplicate_button">"Ðûþļîçåţé - one"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_title_for_share">"Émöţîöñ ĜÎF %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_filename_prefix">"çĥrömé_émöţîöñ_ĝîƒ_%1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_error_asset_fetch">"Çåñ’ţ ðöŵñļöåð réåçţîöñš. Ţrý åĝåîñ. - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_error_screenshot">"Çåñ’ţ ţåķé å šçrééñšĥöţ. Ţrý åĝåîñ. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="lightweight_reactions_error_max_reactions_reached">"Ýöû çåñ åðð ûþ ţö %1$d réåçţîöñš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="screenshot_edit_title">"Éðîţ - one"</string>
<string name="screenshot_delete_title">"Ðéļéţé - one"</string>
<string name="screenshot_save_title">"Šåvé - one"</string>
<string name="screenshot_share_title">"Šĥåré - one"</string>
<string name="screenshot_title_for_share">"Šçrééñšĥöţ %1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="screenshot_filename_prefix">"çĥrömé_šçrééñšĥöţ_%1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="save_image_filename_prefix">"çĥrömé_îmåĝé_%1$s - one two"</string>
<string name="crow_iph">"Šĥöŵ ţĥåñķš ţö ţĥîš çréåţör - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="chime_module_title">"Ĝööĝļé Ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš Þļåţƒörm - one two three"</string>
<string name="image_editor_module_title">"Îmåĝé Éðîţör - one two"</string>
<string name="survey_module_title">"Šûrvéýš - one"</string>
<string name="paint_preview_demo_capture_success">"Paint Preview captured successfully."</string>
<string name="paint_preview_demo_capture_failure">"Failed to capture Paint Preview."</string>
<string name="paint_preview_demo_playback_start">"Displaying Paint Preview."</string>
<string name="paint_preview_demo_playback_failure">"Paint Preview playback failed."</string>
<string name="paint_preview_demo_no_accessibility">"Paint Preview does not have accessibility support."</string>
<string name="paint_preview_startup_upgrade_snackbar_message">"Þrévîéŵîñĝ ţĥîš þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="paint_preview_startup_upgrade_snackbar_action">"®éļöåð - one"</string>
<string name="paint_preview_startup_auto_upgrade_toast">"Vîéŵîñĝ ļîvé þåĝé - one two three"</string>
<string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_1_title">"®éåð ţöðåý\'š ñéŵš 📰 - one two three four"</string>
<string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_1_description">"Årţîçļéš öñ ýöûr îñţéréšţš öñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_2_title">"Šåvé ûþ ţö 60% ðåţå - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_2_description">"Ûšé Ļîţé möðé öñ Ĝööĝļé Çĥrömé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_3_title">"Ĝööĝļé réçömméñðš Çĥrömé - one two three"</string>
<string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_3_description">"Šåvé ûþ ţö 60% ðåţå, réåð ţöðåý\'š ñéŵš - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="notification_permission_rationale_dialog_title">"Çĥrömé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš måķé ţĥîñĝš éåšîér - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="notification_permission_rationale_dialog_message">"Ýöû’ļļ bé åbļé ţö éåšîļý måñåĝé méðîå çöñţröļš, Îñçöĝñîţö šéššîöñš, ðöŵñļöåðš åñð möré - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="notification_permission_rationale_dialog_title_variation_2">"Måñåĝé méðîå çöñţröļš, Îñçöĝñîţö ţåbš, åñð möré ŵîţĥ ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="notification_permission_rationale_dialog_message_variation_2">"Ýöû çåñ ðîšåbļé ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš bý vîšîţîñĝ šéţţîñĝš - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="notification_permission_rationale_accept_button_text">"Çöñţîñûé - one"</string>
<string name="notification_permission_rationale_reject_button_text">"Ñö ţĥåñķš - one two"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_dialog_header">"Ĝéţ îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš¿ - one two three"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_dialog_content">"Îmåĝéš åré šéñţ ţö Ĝööĝļé ţö îmþrövé ðéšçrîþţîöñš ƒör ýöû. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_dialog_option_only_on_wifi">"Öñļý öñ Ŵî-Fî - one two three"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_dialog_get_descriptions_button">"Ĝéţ ðéšçrîþţîöñš - one two"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_settings_title">"Îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš - one two"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_settings_toggle_title">"Ĝéţ îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš - one two three"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_settings_toggle_content">"Šömé îmåĝéš åré šéñţ ţö Ĝööĝļé ţö îmþrövé ðéšçrîþţîöñš ƒör ýöû - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_settings_use_mobile_data_title">"Ûšé möbîļé ðåţå - one two three"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_settings_use_mobile_data_content">"Ŵî-Fî îš ûšéð ŵĥéñ åvåîļåbļé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_toast_off">"Îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš åré öƒƒ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_toast_just_once">"Îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš åððéð ƒör ţĥîš þåĝé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_toast_on">"Îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš åré öñ - one two three four"</string>
<string name="image_descriptions_toast_on_no_wifi">"Îmåĝé ðéšçrîþţîöñš ŵîļļ réšûmé ŵĥéñ ýöû çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_title">"Ĝéţ å béţţér vöîçé éxþérîéñçé öñ ţĥé ŵéb - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_subtitle">"Ĝööĝļé Åššîšţåñţ çåñ çömþļéţé åçţîöñš åçröšš ŵébšîţéš ƒör ýöû - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_body">"Ţö ĥéļþ ýöû çömþļéţé ţåšķš, Ĝööĝļé ŵîļļ réçéîvé ţĥé Û®Ļš åñð çöñţéñţš öƒ šîţéš öñ ŵĥîçĥ ýöû ûšé Åššîšţåñţ, åš ŵéļļ åš îñƒörmåţîöñ ýöû šûbmîţ ţĥröûĝĥ Åššîšţåñţ. Ţĥîš îñƒörmåţîöñ måý bé šţöréð îñ ýöûr Ĝööĝļé åççöûñţ. Ýöû çåñ ţûrñ öƒƒ Åššîšţåñţ îñ Çĥrömé šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_content_description">"Åššîšţåñţ vöîçé šéårçĥ çöñšéñţ ûî - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_half_height_description">"Åššîšţåñţ vöîçé šéårçĥ çöñšéñţ ûî öþéñéð åţ ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_full_height_description">"Åššîšţåñţ vöîçé šéårçĥ çöñšéñţ ûî öþéñéð åţ ƒûļļ ĥéîĝĥţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_closed_description">"Åššîšţåñţ vöîçé šéårçĥ çöñšéñţ ûî çļöšéð - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_simplified_title">"Ĝéţ å béţţér vöîçé éxþérîéñçé - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_simplified_body">"Ķñöŵîñĝ ţĥé Û®Ļš öƒ šîţéš åļļöŵš Ĝööĝļé Åššîšţåñţ ţö ĥéļþ ýöû çömþļéţé ţåšķš. Ýöû çåñ ţûrñ öƒƒ Åššîšţåñţ îñ Çĥrömé šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_simplified_accept">"Ýéš, Î’m îñ - one two three"</string>
<string name="avs_consent_ui_simplified_deny">"Ñö ţĥåñķš - one two"</string>
<string name="avs_setting_category_title">"Vöîçé åššîšţåñçé - one two"</string>
<string name="avs_setting_enabled_title">"Éñĥåñçéð vöîçé šéårçĥ - one two three"</string>
<string name="avs_setting_enabled_description">"Ĝööĝļé Åššîšţåñţ þrövîðéš å béţţér vöîçé éxþérîéñçé ƒör šéårçĥîñĝ ţĥé ŵéb åñð éñĝåĝîñĝ ŵîţĥ šîţéš ýöû ĥåvé öþéñ. Ĝööĝļé Åššîšţåñţ ŵîļļ réçéîvé ţĥé Û®Ļ åñð çöñţéñţš öƒ šîţéš ýöû ûšé ŵîţĥ îţ. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="account_selection_sheet_title_auto">"Signing in to %1$s with %2$s"</string>
<string name="account_selection_sheet_title_explicit">"Šîĝñ îñ ţö %1$s ŵîţĥ %2$s - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent_no_pp_or_tos">"Ţö çöñţîñûé, %1$s ŵîļļ šĥåré ýöûr ñåmé, émåîļ åððréšš, åñð þröƒîļé þîçţûré ŵîţĥ ţĥîš šîţé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent_no_pp">"Ţö çöñţîñûé, %1$s ŵîļļ šĥåré ýöûr ñåmé, émåîļ åððréšš, åñð þröƒîļé þîçţûré ŵîţĥ ţĥîš šîţé. Šéé ţĥîš šîţé\'š &lt;link_terms_of_service&gt;ţérmš öƒ šérvîçé&lt;/link_terms_of_service&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three"</string>
<string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent_no_tos">"Ţö çöñţîñûé, %1$s ŵîļļ šĥåré ýöûr ñåmé, émåîļ åððréšš, åñð þröƒîļé þîçţûré ŵîţĥ ţĥîš šîţé. Šéé ţĥîš šîţé\'š &lt;link_privacy_policy&gt;þrîvåçý þöļîçý&lt;/link_privacy_policy&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two"</string>
<string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent">"Ţö çöñţîñûé, %1$s ŵîļļ šĥåré ýöûr ñåmé, émåîļ åððréšš, åñð þröƒîļé þîçţûré ŵîţĥ ţĥîš šîţé. Šéé ţĥîš šîţé\'š &lt;link_privacy_policy&gt;þrîvåçý þöļîçý&lt;/link_privacy_policy&gt; åñð &lt;link_terms_of_service&gt;ţérmš öƒ šérvîçé&lt;/link_terms_of_service&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="account_selection_continue">"Çöñţîñûé åš %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="account_selection_content_description">"Šîĝñ îñ böţţöm šĥééţ. - one two three four"</string>
<string name="account_selection_sheet_half_height">"Šîĝñ îñ böţţöm šĥééţ öþéñéð åţ ĥåļƒ ĥéîĝĥţ. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="account_selection_sheet_full_height">"Šîĝñ îñ böţţöm šĥééţ öþéñéð åţ ƒûļļ ĥéîĝĥţ. - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="account_selection_sheet_closed">"Šîĝñ îñ böţţöm šĥééţ îš çļöšéð. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="verify_sheet_title">"Vérîƒýîñĝ… - one"</string>
<string name="content_creation_note_title_for_share">"Šţýļîžéð ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ %1$s - one two three"</string>
<string name="content_creation_note_filename_prefix">"çĥrömé_šţýļîžéð_ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ_ - one"</string>
<string name="content_creation_note_template_selected">"%1$s template selected - one"</string>
<string name="content_creation_note_dialog_description">"Šéļéçţ å ţémþļåţé ƒör ýöûr ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ. - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="content_creation_note_shortened_message">"Ĥîĝĥļîĝĥţ ŵåš šĥörţéñéð - one two three"</string>
<string name="quotation_mark_prefix">"“ "</string>
<string name="quotation_mark_suffix">"” "</string>
<string name="settings_https_first_mode_title">"Åļŵåýš ûšé šéçûré çöññéçţîöñš - one two three four"</string>
<string name="settings_https_first_mode_summary">"Ûþĝråðé ñåvîĝåţîöñš ţö ĤŢŢÞŠ åñð ŵårñ ýöû béƒöré ļöåðîñĝ šîţéš ţĥåţ ðöñ’ţ šûþþörţ îţ - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_message_title">"Ðårķ ţĥémé ƒör šîţéš îš öñ îñ Çĥrömé - one two three four five six seven eight"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_message_opt_in_title">"Ðårķ ţĥémé ƒör šîţéš îš åvåîļåbļé - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_message_opt_in_body">"Ýöû çåñ ţûrñ îţ öñ ör öƒƒ îñ šéţţîñĝš - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_message_button">"Öþéñ šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_message_opt_in_button">"Ţûrñ öñ - one two"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_dialog_title">"Šĥåré ƒééðbåçķ öñ ðårķ ţĥémé ƒör šîţéš¿ - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_dialog_message">"Ţéļļ ûš åböûţ ýöûr éxþérîéñçé. Ör &lt;link&gt;çĥåñĝé ýöûr šéţţîñĝš&lt;/link&gt;. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_dialog_positive_button">"Šĥåré ƒééðbåçķ - one two"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_dialog_no_feedback_title">"Çĥåñĝé ýöûr ðårķ ţĥémé šéţţîñĝš¿ - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_dialog_no_feedback_message">"Ýöû çåñ ţûrñ öƒƒ ðårķ ţĥémé ƒör šîţéš îñ ýöûr šéţţîñĝš. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one"</string>
<string name="auto_dark_dialog_no_feedback_positive_button">"Öþéñ šéţţîñĝš - one two"</string>
<string name="managed_browser">"Måñåĝéð bröŵšér - one two"</string>
<string name="management">"Måñåĝéméñţ - one"</string>
<string name="management_subtitle">"Ýöûr bröŵšér îš måñåĝéð bý ýöûr åðmîñîšţråţör - one two three four five six seven"</string>
<string name="management_subtitle_managed_by">"Ýöûr bröŵšér îš måñåĝéð bý %1$s - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="management_not_managed_subtitle">"Ýöûr bröŵšér îš ñöţ måñåĝéð - one two three four five"</string>
<string name="management_browser_notice">"Ýöûr åðmîñîšţråţör çåñ çĥåñĝé ýöûr bröŵšér šéţûþ rémöţéļý. Åçţîvîţý öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé måý åļšö bé måñåĝéð öûţšîðé öƒ Çĥrömé. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="management_learn_more">"&lt;LINK&gt;Ļéårñ Möré&lt;/LINK&gt; - one two three four"</string>
<string name="password_update_dialog_title">"Ûþðåţé þåššŵörð¿ - one two"</string>
<string name="password_edit_dialog_synced_footer_google">"Ýöû çåñ ûšé šåvéð þåššŵörðš öñ åñý ðévîçé. Ţĥéý\'ré šåvéð ţö Ĝööĝļé Þåššŵörð Måñåĝér ƒör %1$s. - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten - one two three four five six"</string>
<string name="password_edit_dialog_unsynced_footer_google">"Þåššŵörðš åré šåvéð ţö Ĝööĝļé Þåššŵörð Måñåĝér öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine ten"</string>
<string name="password_edit_dialog_unsynced_footer">"Þåššŵörðš åré šåvéð ţö Þåššŵörð Måñåĝér öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé - one two three four five six seven eight nine"</string>
<string name="price_drop_spotted_iph">"Þrîçé ðröþ šþöţţéð - one two three"</string>
</resources>
